<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schemas/LocalizationPair.xsd">
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FailureNoExcessFoodDescription">Insufficient Excess Food.</LocalizationPair>

    <!-- Food Rework Game Setting -->
    <LocalizationPair Name="%SettingFoodReworkTitle">Enable Food Rework</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%SettingFoodReworkDescription">Determines whether the ESG Food rework will be enabled. If partially enabled, there will be new empire improvements to convert excess food into other resources. If fully enabled, then population growth will be uncapped by a constructible element</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%SettingFoodReworkTrueTitle">Conversion + Uncapped</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%SettingFoodReworkTrueDescription">You will use ESG food. There will be options to convert excess food into other resources and additional population.</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%SettingFoodReworkPartialTitle">Conversion Only</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%SettingFoodReworkPartialDescription">You will partially use ESG food. There will be options to convert excess food into other resources, but not into additional population.</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%SettingFoodReworkFalseTitle">False</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%SettingFoodReworkFalseDescription">You will use Vanilla food. Excess food will be wasted, and only 1 population can grow per turn.</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementCloneMajorPopulationWithFoodTitle">Population Cloning</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementCloneMajorPopulationWithFoodDescription">Using innovative technologies alongside food surplus it is possible to create population, albeit at an extra cost.</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%QueuedDescriptorIncreasePopulationTitle">Population Cloning</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%QueuedDescriptorIncreasePopulationDescription">Using innovative technologies alongside food surplus it is possible to create population, albeit at an extra cost.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%SystemDefenseDescription">The Garrison represents the ability of the system to repel ground invasions. The [systemDefenseColored] Garrison Manpower and [foodColored] Food Conversion gradually restore this value, while enemy sieges and ground battle losses reduce it.
Excess [systemDefenseColored] Manpower is sent to the [manpowerColored] Empire Manpower stock.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationModifiersTraitSecondaryLuxuryValueTitle">Luxuriously Resourceful</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationModifiersTraitSecondaryStrategicValueTitle">Strategically Resourceful</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- Fixed Tooltip -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GroundBattleBombardmentAttackerDamagesBonusFromCollectionAltTitle">Defensive Bombardment Damage per [population]</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GroundBattleBombardmentAttackerDamagesTitle">Defensive Bombardment Damage</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%GroundBattleBombardmentDefenderDamagesTitle">Offensive Bombardment Damage</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LawEffectP03L00ESGToolTipOverride3">+100 Defensive Bombardment Damage per [population]</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LawEffectP03L00_RepublicESGToolTipOverride3">+150 Defensive Bombardment Damage per [population]</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DepositValueScalesWithGameSpeeed">(Scales with Gamespeed)</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementUniqueStrategicVaultersTooltip">+1 Resource generation on T1 Strategic Deposits on System Level 2
+1 Resource generation on T2 Strategic Deposits on System Level 3
+1 Resource generation on T3 Strategic Deposits on System Level 4
(Scales with Gamespeed)</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Scavenger Hero Skill -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroSkill55_Approval_Perpop_Title">Scavenged Surplus</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroSkill55_Approval_Perpop_Description">Through careful analysis of waste and the appropriate reclamation and filtration techniques, the hero is able to salvage meaningful quantities of resources seemingly out of thin air.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroSkillLuxuryGenerationEffectOverride">Generates 2 luxury resources of each type used in System Development upgrades (no incremental bonus for luxuries used more than once)</LocalizationPair>


  <!-- Unfallen Capstone Skill -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroSkillPopulationBoostsOverride2">+50% effect from [fidsi] and [happinessColored] Racial Bonuses</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- Population Modifiers -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationModifiersTraitSecondaryCustomGroundBattleBombardmentAttackerDamagesPerMinorFaction00Title">Federal Defensive Damage</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationModifiersTraitSecondaryCustomGroundBattleBombardmentAttackerDamagesPerMinorFaction00TooltipOverride">+25 Defensive Bombardment Damage on Population per Minor Faction Assimilated</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationModifiersTraitSecondaryCustomGroundBattleBombardmentAttackerDamagesPerBackdoor00Title">Duplicitous Defensive Damage</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationModifiersTraitSecondaryCustomGroundBattleBombardmentAttackerDamagesPerBackdoor00TooltipOverride">+25 Defensive Bombardment Damage during ground battle on Population per Backdoor</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationModifiersTraitSecondaryCustomGroundBattleBombardmentAttackerDamagesPerTemple00Title">Fanatical Defensive Damage</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationModifiersTraitSecondaryCustomGroundBattleBombardmentAttackerDamagesPerSystemLevel00Title">Modernized Defensive Damage</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationModifiersTraitSecondaryCustomGroundBattleBombardmentAttackerDamagesLevel00TooltipOverride">+15 Defensive Bombardment Damage on Population per System Level</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Faction Pacts -->
    <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionPactEffectSophonsDescription">This is an agreement to share faction advantages with the Sophon.
Your faction will gain +0.83% [scienceColored] on Systems per Turn [turn] (Max: 25%), increase scales with game speed.</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityGameplaySophonsTooltipEffect">A science bonus is given for discovering technologies based on how many players have already researched it: the fewer know it, the higher the reduction on the next research.
  
Starting Ships: 1x [colonizer], 1x [explorer]
Faction Pact: +0.83% [scienceColored] per [turn] (Max: 25%)</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionPactEffectTimeLordsDescription">This is an agreement to share faction advantages with the Riftborn.
Your faction will gain +0.67% [industryColored] on Systems per Turn [turn] (Max: 20%), increase scales with game speed.</LocalizationPair>
    <LocalizationPair Name="%AffinityGameplayTimeLordsTooltipEffect">Can build Singularities, and affect time by placing them on a system. 
Singularities have a fixed duration and can only be placed on a system within the empire's vision
  
Starting Ships: 1x [colonizer], 1x [explorer]
Faction Pact: +0.67% [industryColored] per [turn] (Max: 20%)</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Nakalim -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StrategicBonusFromCollectionAltTitle">Resource Generation on Strategic Resource Deposit</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LawP00L05TemplarsTooltipOverride">-2 [happinessColored] per [population] on Planets with Temples</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LawP00L05TemplarsTitle">Scrupulous Scientific Examination of Cultural Artifacts</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LawP00L05TemplarsDescription">The relics of the past are a thing to be studied using the scientific method! By providing research institutions the ability to get their hands on our relics, we will be ushering in an age known only to our ancestors! Our believers may protest the sacrilege of converting their places of worships into a science fair, but one must make way for progress.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%LawP00L05TemplarsShortTitle">Research Reliquaries Act</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%NumberOfTemplesTitle">Temples</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- Vaulters -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUnique11SuperColonizerESGTitle">Enhanced Argosy Hull</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUnique11SuperColonizerTitle">Mobile Wormhole Concentrators</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementVaultersArgosyEnhancementTooltipEffect">Allows the Argosy to consume all Movement Points to act as a Mobile Portal
Argosy can can Fleets at Level 1 without Modules</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementUnique11VaultersEffect">Portal use costs only 1 Movement Point (Bonus also applies to allies with the Metafolding Affinity)</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Cravers -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDust1CraversTitle">Xenobiological Incentives</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDust1CraversDescription">Divided between cold and disinterested masters and their slaves, Craver society can offer few incentives to its denizens. However, by exploiting luxuries as a reward for collaborators and additives for the main Craver population, a profitable system of incentives can still be achieved.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementFood2CraversTitle">Alternative Food Programs</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementFood2CraversDescription">Both Cravers and their victims long ago realized that eating the labor force was not a good long term plan, and so food growing programs were created to take advantage of a planets natural biosphere for more efficient and sustainable fueling of the war machine.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementBuyout1CraversTitle">Expendable Dust Expertise</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementBuyout1CraversDescription">Dust-empowered individuals are few and far between, but not too difficult to find during the food conversion process. By removing both Craver and conquered from the population when these talents show themselves, we can maintain an elite Dust labor force who shall live short, but significantly more pleasant lives until the construction efforts burn them out.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementInfluence1CraversTitle">Conquest Announcement Networks</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementInfluence1CraversDescription">Cravers and their slaves derive little joy from the empires progress, but by hooking the former into a mental network and giving the latter constant updates from screens and speakers, every achievement can heighten the excitement of the Cravers and beat down the hope of their victims in real-time.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementInfluence2CraversTitle">Body Language Programming</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementInfluence2CraversDescription">By obtaining other factions guides to diplomacy and facial recognition databases, we can create Craver specialists programmed to identify and exploit not only the emotional responses of other factions, but also of conquered populations who might be more amenable to the carrot or the stick at any moment.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementScience6CraversTitle">Evolutionary Analysis Pens</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementScience6CraversDescription">One of the limits of natural evolution is that it cannot handle large changes well, as species are wiped out by disasters or predators which are too great a difference for them - Predators like the Cravers. By setting aside entire continents to only ever be attacked by Craver scouts and raiding parties that they can just about handle, we can observe our own weaknesses in an arena where our economy of scale will not obscure the results.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementInfluence3CraversTitle">Intergalactic Hostages</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementInfluence3CraversDescription">By establishing "foreign exchange" arrangements with allies and offering hits of Dust-9 to famous figures in other empires, the Cravers can offer significant incentives to foreign politicians as an incentive to collaborate, and the threat of punishing famous prisoners and entire populations of their distant relatives as a convenient threat to prevent war without ruining the reputation of said politicians at home.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementIndustry5CraversTitle">Hazardous Mining Hives</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementIndustry5CraversDescription">Through intense experimentation, we have created an offshoot of the Craver species whose birth is caused by the chemical triggers of valuable strategic resources. Cheap, tough, and tireless, these worker drone hives are well suited to the most dangerous of environments.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementScienceOnGasCraversTitle">Collaborative Research Academies</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementScienceOnGasCraversDescription">While it is dangerous to allow educated members of the empire and its victims such unrestricted access to one another, giving scientists and their families exemption from hard labor in return for working with Craver scientists can prove a boon, especially when provided with expendable Craver assistants which will not complain about radiation or experimentation.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDust7CraversTitle">Dust-Consuming Collectors</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementDust7CraversDescription">By putting a new variety of cheap, expendable Dust-consuming Cravers under the command of regular Cravers with a mastery of Dust, we can mine vast amounts of it at extremely low cost using these self-sustaining mini-hives of hungerless workers and clairvoyant overseers.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementScience8CraversTitle">Aerial Drone Deployments</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementScience8CraversDescription">Cravers are a heavy species, not least due to being cyborgs, and that can make life on a gas giant more difficult. While they are no longer recognizable as Cravers and make the rest of their species uncomfortable, prefab hives of dormant aerial drones can be deployed to harvest and explore these worlds as though they were native to the environment.</LocalizationPair>
</Datatable>