<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">

  <!-- <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyEndlessWonder1EnhancedTitle">Husk of Knowledge (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair> -->
  <!-- <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyEndlessWonder1EnhancedDescription">Auriga housed the greatest site for the study of xenobiology ever created by the genius of the Endless. A towering achievement of industry and science, the surface and crust of the planet were a warren of laboratories, biospheres, and research centers. When the bombs fell during the Dust Wars, this enormous installation became the greatest expanse of ruins - and store of lost knowledge - in the known galaxy. Should the laboratories ever be repaired and the data recovered, the scientific benefit would be unimaginable.</LocalizationPair> -->
  <!-- <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyEndlessWonder2EnhancedTitle">Spotora's Sanctum (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair> -->
  <!-- <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyEndlessWonder2EnhancedDescription">Also known as the Icarael's Watch, this is the one laboratory in all of the Endless-controlled galaxy that had the best claim to the discovery of the science of virtualization. Spotora Ortamm and her team are credited with the first consistent, replicable method for the virtualization of a sentient mind; the notes and equipment have enormous value in spite of their age.</LocalizationPair> -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly01EnhancedTitle">Garden of Eden (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly01EnhancedDescription">Lush and pleasant, with a single year-round season of moderate temperatures, life is good on this planet. Everyone benefits from its natural wealth: Residents, tourists, businessmen, and scientists.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly02EnhancedTitle">Dust Ruins (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly02EnhancedDescription">Many ruins from the time of the Endless were Dust-enhanced structures or traditional buildings that preceded the Dust era. On very rare occasions, however, one can find entire structures built uniquely from this valuable resource.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly03EnhancedTitle">Friendly Locals (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly03EnhancedDescription">Native inhabitants can be classified in one of two ways: those who view you as friends, and those who view you as dinner. Fortunately, this is the former case. By accelerating the colonists' adaptation to the local ecosystem, they permit a higher density of population than is common on a planet of this size.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly04EnhancedTitle">Rich Soil (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly04EnhancedDescription">The soil of this planet is rich in bacteria and nutrients; crops will grow well and livestock will be healthy.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly05EnhancedTitle">Mineral Rich (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly05EnhancedDescription">Due to its formation from Dust clouds that spun off from the system's sun, the crust of this planet is unusually rich in minerals.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly06EnhancedTitle">Hadopelagic Life (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly06EnhancedDescription">Having deep oceans that are rich with life, this planet is abundant in hadopelagic creatures -- those that have adapted to the lightless environment at the bottom of the ocean and are tolerant of the tremendous pressures. They are not only a source of food, but provide useful scientific information on extremophilic life forms.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly07EnhancedTitle">Antonov Rings (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly07EnhancedDescription">Dense rings of beige and brown asteroids with erratic orbits, the planetary rings are fascinating for tourists and equally interesting for scientific studies.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly08EnhancedTitle">Huygens Rings (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly08EnhancedDescription">A rich, multi-colored band of asteroids surrounds this planet. Reflecting the star's light in green, gray, purple, white, and blue, they are a highly prized tourist destination as well as a ready source of minerals and alloys.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly09EnhancedTitle">Hollow Planet (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly09EnhancedDescription">About as anomalous as an anomaly can be, this planet has vast subterranean spaces that are hundreds of cubic kilometers in size. Fascinating to tourists and scientists, it adds a great deal of habitable space that is highly defensible.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly10EnhancedTitle">Ice-10 (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly10EnhancedDescription">A rare form of ice that is caused by water crystallizing under high pressures, Ice-10 is interesting for its thermodynamic properties. A concerted effort by the planet's engineers has led to a lessening of its negative effects.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly11EnhancedTitle">Permanent Monsoon (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly11EnhancedDescription">Once a very wet and very difficult environment, a concerted effort to partially terraform the planet has lessened the intensity of the winds and storms.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly12EnhancedTitle">Metallic Waters (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly12EnhancedDescription">Almost dirt-free, the hard, gleaming surface of this planet used to make agriculture difficult and potentially poisonous. Recent improvements in soil development, however, have eased the problem.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly13EnhancedTitle">Aurora Waves (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly13EnhancedDescription">The gleaming, multi-colored auroras that once caused such headaches have been partially tamed by magnetic shielding. Fortunately, their beauty remains even though their negative effects have been reduced.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly14EnhancedTitle">Dense Atmosphere (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly14EnhancedDescription">Lava planets in particular, due to the continual combustion and high temperature of their crust, have atmospheres that are dense in organic compounds. Though it renders them a challenge to colonize, this anomaly also helps to increase the agricultural output.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly15EnhancedTitle">Psychoactive Air (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly15EnhancedDescription">With an atmosphere that was once saturated by complex chemical compounds, life on this planet was challenging. Application of terraforming technologies, however, has rendered the effects of the air less intense.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly16EnhancedTitle">Geothermic Activity (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly16EnhancedDescription">Applying enormous amounts of energy and grappling with gravitational alterations, the previously uncontrollable geothermic activity of the planet is now somewhat less intense.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly17EnhancedTitle">Seismic Activity (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly17EnhancedDescription">By manipulating the magnetic core, stabilizing continental drift, and improving construction techniques, the problems in daily life caused by seismic activity have been notably reduced.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- 18 is Long Season (Negative)  -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly19EnhancedTitle">Meteor Strikes (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly19EnhancedDescription">For the first time in the history of the universe, the phrase "killer satellites" actually has a practical meaning. Thanks to cheap and robust sources of energy and heavily shielded orbitals, major meteor threats are neutralized high in the atmosphere.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- 20 is Polar Tempests (Negative) -->
  <!-- 21 is Strong Magnetic Field (Negative) -->
  <!-- 22 is Kessler Syndrome (Negative) -->
  <!-- 23 is Acid Rain (Negative) -->
  <!-- 24 is Irradiated (Negative) -->
  <!-- 25-27 are moons  -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly28EnhancedTitle">Hostile Fauna (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly28EnhancedDescription">While the beasts of this planet were first described as "giant," "primal," and "impressive," these days the adjectives would tend to "controlled," "manageable," and "delicious."</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly29EnhancedTitle">Ancient Ruins (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly29EnhancedDescription">Search teams discover ruins of one of the many ancient civilizations that have risen and fallen since the birth of the universe. Trade, tourism, and research could potentially benefit from this rare find.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly30EnhancedTitle">Dust Lode (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly30EnhancedDescription">Once a base or battleground of the Endless civilization, their nanotechnological 'Dust' is omnipresent in the ground and atmosphere.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly31EnhancedTitle">Coral Reefs (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly31EnhancedDescription">Picturesque, rich, and fascinating, these lush reefs beautify the planet, provide sources of food, and are of interest to tourists (once they have been declared either non-lethal or only partially lethal).</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly32EnhancedTitle">Cyber Flora (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly32EnhancedDescription">A hybrid species that grew from Dust-infected lichen, this nearly indestructible plant can be found thriving even in the harshest conditions. Its beautiful, glossy sheen and interesting bio-technical properties create both a stunning environment and a source of scientific knowledge.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly33EnhancedTitle">Strange Fossils (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly33EnhancedDescription">What strange beasts were these! Science Officers have discovered the remains of long-dead creatures that appear exceptional in every way -- size, variety, eating habits, and number of limbs. Anthropologists and cosmologists are eager to study these finds</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly34EnhancedTitle">Microfactories (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly34EnhancedDescription">Another innovation of the Endless, some Visited planets were sown with these Dust-built millimeter-scale factories that convert mineral solids into nutrient chains for crops. Adaptable or 'trainable' to a wide range of ecosystems, they are an enormous boon to food production and agricultural labor.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly35EnhancedTitle">Mutated Flora (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly35EnhancedDescription">An example of biodiversity gone berserk, this planet shows a variety of plant mutations of every size, shape, color, scent, flavor, and psychoactive effect that one could imagine. Some of the more notable results include rich food supplies and ecstatic gourmet chefs.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly36EnhancedTitle">Low Gravity (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly36EnhancedDescription">A lower density of planetary core effects many things, of which gravity is the most notable. This has advantages for industrial production and makes kids really, really happy.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly37EnhancedTitle">Deserted Cities (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly37EnhancedDescription">An eerie reminder of yet another lost civilization, deserted cities are scattered across the surface of this planet. Even stranger, many of the buildings and machines are still in working order. If a planet had been conceived to make scientists and engineers happy, it is this one.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly38EnhancedTitle">Molten Springs (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly38EnhancedDescription">Blessed--or cursed--by volcanic activity close to the surface and a metal-rich crust, geysers of molten metal spew their very dangerous and very valuable contents from numerous points on the planet. Industry and commerce can clearly benefit from this bizarre geology.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly39EnhancedTitle">Shattered Crust (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly39EnhancedDescription">The surface of this planet is a riot of cliffs, chasms, ridges, and spikes. While the broken surface means that many mineral resources can be easily mined, it also means that transport and construction will be challenging.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly40EnhancedTitle">Komatiite Volcano (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly40EnhancedDescription">Dude, where's my silica? These volcanoes of ultramafic rock from deep within the planet's mantle are sources of useful metal alloys, and can be cheaply exploited for geothermal energy.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly41EnhancedTitle">Propitious Seasons (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly41EnhancedDescription">This is not merely a planet that has the benefit of an axial tilt that produces seasonal variations in weather; the seasons and their associated climates lend themselves well to agriculture.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly42EnhancedTitle">Humeris Insidentes (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly42EnhancedDescription">This planet was inhabited by a highly advanced race that died off when a massive volcanic eruption induced a prolonged winter. The knowledge of their civilization was meticulously documented and stored in bunkers scattered across the planet. Clearly, they expected to rise up after the winter and continue their evolution. Sadly, the bunkers sit unlocked and unused, and the people have returned to the dust. Their knowledge, however, is yours to explore.</LocalizationPair>
  
    <!-- 43 is Poor Soil (Negative)  -->
	<!-- 44 is High Gravity (Negative)  -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly45EnhancedTitle">Behemoth Song (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly45EnhancedDescription">This strange planet emits natural sound and magnetic waves that imitate musical frequencies. The melodies can only be heard by ships in orbit with all electronics powered off, and their poignant beauty is said to be overwhelming.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly46EnhancedTitle">Talking World (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly46EnhancedDescription">There is a continual series of radio wave transmission from variable sites on the planet. Though they appear to be artificial and thus have some purpose, the transmitters have yet to be identified and the code or language remains an unsolved mystery.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly47EnhancedTitle">Fearful Symmetry (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly47EnhancedDescription">The planet's features exhibit a bilateral symmetry that is unnatural for its mathematical precision. One can only speculate as to what lies underneath the outer layers to cause this.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly48EnhancedTitle">High-Energy Plasmasphere (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly48EnhancedDescription">A high-energy planetary ionosphere generates a particularly powerful plasma shield that naturally deflects incoming charged particles or projectiles. This field is not only a boon for scientific study, but is also a great source of natural energy as it can be harnessed as a continuous power source.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- CRESCENT ANOMALIES -->
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly50EnhancedTitle">Artificial Life (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly50EnhancedDescription">Maybe it is the combination of billions of precise factors, or maybe it is pure luck, but every attempt to create artificial life on this Crescent seems to succeed.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly51EnhancedTitle">Dust Accretor (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly51EnhancedDescription">Large quantities of Dust can be found in the dark nooks of this Crescent, as some of the materials used in its construction seem to attract ambient Dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly52EnhancedTitle">Flickering Matter (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly52EnhancedDescription">As a material construction created by an immaterial being, sometimes this Crescent flickers and loses its materiality for a few moments. Although this is fortuitous for the understanding of matter itself, it may not be such good news when what you are trying to build disappears unpredictably.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly53EnhancedTitle">Pseudo-Atmosphere (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly53EnhancedDescription">A pseudo-atmosphere appeared during the creation of this Crescent. The way light passes through it creates unique visuals, so fascinating that even the most scientific minds tend to become aesthetes.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- WONDER ANOMALIES -->
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder1EnhancedTitle">Dust Nebula (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder1EnhancedDescription">A warning beacon into the entire nebula rich with Dust tells its story. Due to poorly-controlled research, a strain of Dust ran wild and self-replicated out of control. By the time it was reined in, entire planetary systems had been converted to Dust, and no food remained for the handful of surviving researchers that left that grim note.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder2EnhancedTitle">The Seventeen Thousand Islands Bridge (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder2EnhancedDescription">An archipelago of natural islands that span the gap between planet surface and space, hanging in the darkness like glittering stepping stones. The source of the power that maintains the islands in position is unknown, but many speculate that Endless technology is responsible.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder3EnhancedTitle">The Fallen Gardens (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder3EnhancedDescription">A space graveyard for vast structures of unknown provenance, the Fallen Gardens are a twilight world of ancient technology long forgotten and dormant. Some speculate the structures are starships of once-marvelous engineering now consigned to rust, strange mottled patches of fungus and vegetation crawling across their surfaces. Others claim they are the sloughed skins of Gods. What is certain is that the gardens are far from dead.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder4EnhancedTitle">The Platform of Ys (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder4EnhancedDescription">The world was once the greatest shipyard of the concrete Endless. The skies above the planet darkened with the enormous spacedocks that worked day and night, building and repairing fleets. While much of the technology is lost, the platforms still provide both living space and planetary defense.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder5EnhancedTitle">Tree of Worlds (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder5EnhancedDescription">Originally a thing of branch and root, this hyper-grown life form reaches from deep within the planetary crust out into space. A strange, unique artifact of some biological experiment gone berserk, this "tree" houses cities and river systems, mines and farms. Certain heavily mutated branches even reach out into the vacuum of space, filtering Dust and minerals to feed its always-hungry limbs.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder6EnhancedTitle">Tunneled Slipgates (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder6EnhancedDescription">A natural anomaly whose probable existence is less than zero, this series of natural quantum-linked transport gates create “tunnels” from the planets’ surfaces to various points in the star system. This piece of space-time is full of bridges, shortcuts and holes, allowing rapid transport throughout the system.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- RUIN ANOMALIES - REDUCED -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeReducedTitle">Large Debris Field (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeReducedDescription">The site of a major engagement between warring empires, the space surrounding this system is filled with debris of all types and sizes.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumReducedTitle">Medium Debris Field (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumReducedDescription">The site of an engagement between enemy fleets, there are noticeable chunks of debris floating in the system's space.</LocalizationPair>
  
    <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallReducedTitle">Small Debris Field (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallReducedDescription">Twisted metal remains and scorched plastics drift here, a reminder of a previous skirmish.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionReducedTitle">Pre-galactic Architecture (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionReducedDescription">A minor civilization that resisted assimilation was conquered here, and signs of the battles remain.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeReducedTitle">Gutted Pirate Stronghold (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeReducedDescription">A thriving pirate colony was laid to waste here, resulting in massive devastation and debris.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumReducedTitle">Gutted Pirate Lair (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumReducedDescription">There was once a pirate hideout here, but only ruins and debris remain.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallReducedTitle">Gutted Pirate Hideout (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallReducedDescription">A small band of pirates once held this place, but they were driven out and only some debris remains.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeReducedTitle">Apocalyptic Landscape (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeReducedDescription">An enormous ground battle occurred here, and the planet will forever show the horrific scars.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumReducedTitle">Devastation (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumReducedDescription">A ground battle took place here, and the planet is only slowly recovering.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallReducedTitle">Trenches (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallReducedDescription">A minor engagement occurred here, but the evidence of battle is already disappearing.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- RUIN ANOMALIES - ENHANCED -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeEnhancedTitle">Large Debris Field (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeEnhancedDescription">The site of a major engagement between warring empires, the space surrounding this system is filled with debris of all types and sizes.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumEnhancedTitle">Medium Debris Field (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumEnhancedDescription">The site of an engagement between enemy fleets, there are noticeable chunks of debris floating in the system's space.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallEnhancedTitle">Small Debris Field (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallEnhancedDescription">Twisted metal remains and scorched plastics drift here, a reminder of a previous skirmish.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionEnhancedTitle">Pre-galactic Architecture (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionEnhancedDescription">A minor civilization that resisted assimilation was conquered here, and signs of the battles remain.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeEnhancedTitle">Gutted Pirate Stronghold (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeEnhancedDescription">A thriving pirate colony was laid to waste here, resulting in massive devastation and debris.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumEnhancedTitle">Gutted Pirate Lair (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumEnhancedDescription">There was once a pirate hideout here, but only ruins and debris remain.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallEnhancedTitle">Gutted Pirate Hideout (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallEnhancedDescription">A small band of pirates once held this place, but they were driven out and only some debris remains.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeEnhancedTitle">Apocalyptic Landscape (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeEnhancedDescription">An enormous ground battle occurred here, and the planet will forever show the horrific scars.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumEnhancedTitle">Devastation (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumEnhancedDescription">A ground battle took place here, and the planet is only slowly recovering.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallEnhancedTitle">Trenches (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallEnhancedDescription">A minor engagement occurred here, but the evidence of battle is already disappearing.</LocalizationPair>

</Datatable>