<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">

  <!-- Permanent Monsoon - Currently +2f/pop, -2h/pop, -2i/pop -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly11Description">The good news: This is a water-rich planet and therefore of great value to agriculture. The bad news: This water is generally delivered horizontally in your face by gale-force winds, flooding roads and making the population wet and miserable.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Metallic Waters - currently +1i/pop, -1f/pop, -2h/pop-->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly12Description">Rich in deposits of copper, iron, zinc, and other metals, the lakes and geysers of this planet are stunning to behold but intolerable to plant life. At least the high metal content of the waters is a boon to industrial development, as highly purified ores can be obtained through simple filtration.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Long season - currently -1d/pop -1f/pop -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly18Description">With an unusually long orbital ellipse, the planet has very long seasons and thus is exposed to extremes of cold in winter and heat in summer. While a few people insist you "get used to it", the weather is challenging for agriculture and raises the cost of living.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <!-- Ancient Ruins - currently +4dust/pop -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly29Description">Search teams discover ruins of one of the many ancient civilizations that have risen and fallen since the birth of the universe. Although primitive, the structures are beautiful, and the tourism industry could benefit greatly from this rare find.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly01Title">Enhance Garden of Eden</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly01Description">Start up a think-tank, working out how you can possibly make this world even nicer than it already is.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly01EnhancedTitle">Garden of Eden</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly01EnhancedDescription">The hardest thing about enhancing this planet was working out how a perfect world could be made even better. Ultimately, your ecologists took a different approach - the planet's mild seasons and lack of significant tectonic activity made it ideal for construction of a series of delicate climate-controlled domes, exhibiting the ecologies of countless other worlds from parched deserts to frozen tundras.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly02Title">Enhance Dust Ruins</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly02Description">Cordon off the dust ruins and study them, before someone plunders them for their riches.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly02EnhancedTitle">Dust Ruins</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly02EnhancedDescription">Although the first instinct of the local industry leaders was to plunder the Dust ruins for their riches, long-term thinking prevailed, and they were instead carefully excavated and exhibited for the benefit of all.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly03Title">Enhance Friendly Locals</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly03Description">Work with the native population to build a more multicultural society.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly03EnhancedTitle">Friendly Locals</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly03EnhancedDescription">Integrating the planet's native people and culture into their society from the start, and acting as guests rather than colonizers, this world's population have become more accepting of others. The multicultural society here is a wonderful working environment for all the myriad species of your empire.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly04Title">Enhance Rich Soil</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly04Description">Develop new farming techniques specific to this planet and its unique soil composition.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly04EnhancedTitle">Rich Soil</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly04EnhancedDescription">While ultra-intensive farming techniques risked depleting even the bountiful soil of this world, a study of rainforest plants and soil bacteria found ways to efficiently renew all the nutrients. The planet's food productivity is remarkable.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly05Title">Enhance Mineral Deposits</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly05Description">Exploit this planet's rich mineral deposits.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly05EnhancedTitle">Mineral Rich</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly05EnhancedDescription">The planet's bountiful crust has been a blessing for the economy, once the initial lawless free-for-all was reined in. Now, land deeds are correctly recorded, deep-mining operations appropriately regulated, and even most of the original pollution has been cleaned up.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly06Title">Enhance Hadopelagic Life</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly06Description">Construct a deep-sea laboratory to study the planet's remarkable oceanic life.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly06EnhancedTitle">Hadopelagic Life</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly06EnhancedDescription">It took a lot of doing, given the frankly murderous pressures involved, but your empire succeeded in constructing an ultra-deep-sea laboratory to study this planet's unique life-forms. People being as they are, it was soon followed by the galaxy's deepest underwater hotel, a lunatic endeavor that has nevertheless been pulling in tourists from far and wide.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly07Title">Enhance Antonov Rings</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly07Description">Construct a swarm of gatherer satellites to harvest valuable Dust from the planetary rings.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly07EnhancedTitle">Antonov Rings</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly07EnhancedDescription">Believed to have been formed from the shattered  remains of a once-colonized moon, this asteroid band is a rich source of Dust, and fascinating to the scientific community.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly08Title">Enhance Huygens Rings</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly08Description">Construct a swarm of research satellites to study the planetary rings.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly08EnhancedTitle">Huygens Rings</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly08EnhancedDescription">The remains of the protoplanetary disc, and now laced through with research satellites, this asteroid band is a unique glimpse into planet formation.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly09Title">Enhance Hollow Planet</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly09Description">Explore the cave network and begin putting these remarkable underground spaces to use.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly09EnhancedTitle">Hollow Planet</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly09EnhancedDescription">Although new, deeper caves are still being discovered to this day, the majority of the planet's vast caverns have been explored, reinforced, studied, and repurposed for industry, research, or some of the galaxy's most unique housing.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly10Title">Enhance Ice-10</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly10Description">Study the mysteries of Ice-10, and see if you can make use of it.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly10EnhancedTitle">Ice-10</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly10EnhancedDescription">A rare form of ice that is caused by water crystallizing under high pressures, Ice-10 is interesting for its thermodynamic properties - which have been thoroughly studied, such that the fascinating substance can now be used in superconductor construction.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly11Title">Enhance Permanent Monsoon</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly11Description">Develop new crop species that can thrive in the monsoon weather.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly11EnhancedTitle">Permanent Monsoon</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly11EnhancedDescription">Once a very wet and very difficult environment, a concerted effort to partially terraform the planet has lessened the intensity of the winds and storms - and developed some of your empire's most productive farms.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly12Title">Enhance Metallic Waters</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly12Description">Roll out a line of artificial soil microbes that can tolerate the planet's conditions.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly12EnhancedTitle">Metallic Waters</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly12EnhancedDescription">Almost dirt-free, the hard, gleaming surface of this planet used to make agriculture difficult and potentially poisonous. Newly-developed artificial soil microbes not only sequester toxic metal salts from the water, but package and serve them up on a silver platter for local chemical industries.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly13Title">Enhance Aurora Waves</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly13Description">Promote a new tourist industry on this beautiful planet.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly13EnhancedTitle">Aurora Waves</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly13EnhancedDescription">The gleaming, multi-colored auroras that once caused such headaches have been tamed by magnetic shielding. Their beauty remains undisturbed, and draws tourists from far and wide.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly14Title">Enhance Dense Atmosphere</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly14Description">Selectively breed new macrofauna to take advantage of the dense atmosphere.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly14EnhancedTitle">Dense Atmosphere</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly14EnhancedDescription">As any xenobiologist knows, a denser atmosphere is one of the requirements for animal life to grow to gargantuan sizes. This planet once lacked such titans, but through selective breeding, you now have some beasts big enough that you can put the pasture on them rather than the other way around.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly15Title">Enhance Psychoactive Air</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly15Description">Set up a network of filtration systems to reduce the effects of the planet's atmosphere on your populace.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly15EnhancedTitle">Psychoactive Air</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly15EnhancedDescription">With an atmosphere that was once saturated by complex chemical compounds, life on this planet was challenging. These days, vast filtration stations ensure that the various psychoactive compounds are available only when they're desirable.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly16Title">Enhance Geothermic Activity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly16Description">Sink thermal rods deep into the planet's crust to tap the geothermal heat and reduce volcanic hazards.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly16EnhancedTitle">Geothermic Activity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly16EnhancedDescription">Applying enormous amounts of energy and grappling with gravitational alterations, the previously uncontrollable geothermic activity of the planet is not only manageable, but actually useful since every new factory can have its own dedicated geothermal generator.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly17Title">Enhance Seismic Activity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly17Description">Power up a deep-crust network of gravitational flux columns to tame the planet's seismic forces.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly17EnhancedTitle">Seismic Activity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly17EnhancedDescription">By manipulating the magnetic core, stabilizing continental drift, and improving construction techniques, the problems in daily life caused by seismic activity have been largely solved - and on top of this, some amazing new scientific developments came out of the project.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- 18 is Long Season (Negative)  -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly18Title">Convert Long Season</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly18Description">It might seem like a mad endeavour, but you have enough power at your disposal - change the planet's axial tilt, and make the seasons more bearable!</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly19Title">Enhance Meteor Strikes</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly19Description">Upgrade your defensive satellite network to capture and mine the meteors.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly19EnhancedTitle">Meteor Strikes</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly19EnhancedDescription">The previously named "killer satellites" are now less like assassins and more like goalkeepers. Thanks to cheap and robust sources of energy and innovations in shield technology, incoming meteors are captured and mined for their valuable ore deposits.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- 20 is Polar Tempests (Negative) -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly20Title">Convert Polar Tempests</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly20Description">Ramp up the climate control until the polar tempests subside entirely. This will make the atmosphere much denser overall, and more amenable to crop growth.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- 21 is Strong Magnetic Field (Negative) -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly21Title">Convert Strong Magnetic Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly21Description">Take advantage of the naturally strong magnetic field to create a defensive plasmasphere over the entire planet.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- 22 is Kessler Syndrome (Negative) -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly22Title">Convert Kessler Syndrome</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly22Description">Sweep the orbital debris into neat (and attractive) rings.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- 23 is Acid Rain (Negative) -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly23Title">Convert Acid Rain</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly23Description">With the acid rain under control, maybe those volcanic fumaroles can be made useful for industry?</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- 24 is Irradiated (Negative) -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly24Title">Convert Irradiation</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly24Description">Study the plant-life of this once-irradiated world, and see what bounty you find.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- 25-27 are moons  -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly28Title">Enhance Hostile Fauna</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly28Description">Domesticate this planet's magnificent predatory beasts.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly28EnhancedTitle">Hostile Fauna</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly28EnhancedDescription">While the beasts of this planet were first described as "giant," "primal," and "impressive," these days the adjectives would tend to "companionable," "obedient," and "just the right size to ride on."</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly29Title">Enhance Ancient Ruins</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly29Description">Excavate and study the ancient ruins.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly29EnhancedTitle">Ancient Ruins</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly29EnhancedDescription">The ruins here have been painstakingly excavated, and regrettably, we must conclude that the former inhabitants of this planet were a primitive, pre-electricity species, whose scientific knowledge offers us nothing new. However, the excavated ruins are breathtaking in their beauty, and tourism is booming.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly30Title">Enhance Dust Lode</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly30Description">Chart the dust lodes and try to find out where they're coming from.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly30EnhancedTitle">Dust Lode</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly30EnhancedDescription">By following the traces of Dust embedded in the world's crust, our scientists have uncovered - and repurposed - the fortified subterranean bases of the Endless that put it there.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly31Title">Enhance Coral Reefs</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly31Description">Set up a conservation programme to preserve the natural beauty of the coral reefs.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly31EnhancedTitle">Coral Reefs</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly31EnhancedDescription">This world's carefully-conserved coral reefs are now a symbol of natural beauty recognised galaxy-wide.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly32Title">Enhance Cyber Flora</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly32Description">Study the odd cybernetic flora, and see if it can be put to good use.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly32EnhancedTitle">Cyber Flora</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly32EnhancedDescription">The so called "cyber-lichen" turns out to form a natural neural network under certain conditions. This allows for vital components of research mainframes and espionage supercomputers to be grown on agar plates rather than built.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly33Title">Enhance Strange Fossils</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly33Description">Study the fossils, and see if they can become more than just a curiosity.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly33EnhancedTitle">Strange Fossils</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly33EnhancedDescription">Your scientists have discovered connections between the ecology of the ancient, now-fossilised organisms here and the mineral deposits in the system. Working from this knowledge, new resource veins can be uncovered.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly34Title">Enhance Microfactories</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly34Description">Study the atmospheric microfactories, and see if they can be controlled.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly34EnhancedTitle">Microfactories</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly34EnhancedDescription">Now that the control codes for the Endless microfactories have been deciphered, their effects on food production can be boosted.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly35Title">Enhance Mutated Flora</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly35Description">Catalogue the world's extensive array of mutant flora.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly35EnhancedTitle">Mutated Flora</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly35EnhancedDescription">We've finally catalogued exactly which of the absurd profusion of flora on this planet are toxic, allergenic, or violently motile. The gourmet food industry is more diverse than ever, and being an experimental chef requires less hazard pay.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly36Title">Enhance Low Gravity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly36Description">Adapt the local architecture to take advantage of the low gravity.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly36EnhancedTitle">Low Gravity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly36EnhancedDescription">Local architecture has adapted to take advantage of the low gravity - soaring bridges and towering needle-like spires are the order of the day, and all available with low-cost materials.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly37Title">Enhance Deserted Cities</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly37Description">Conduct archaeological studies of the deserted cities.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly37EnhancedTitle">Deserted Cities</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly37EnhancedDescription">With the archaeologists' work finally finished, reconstruction and resettlement of the world's deserted cities has begun. Many buildings have been preserved in their original state, as monuments to those who came before, while others become industrial centres or research institutes.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly38Title">Enhance Molten Springs</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly38Description">Build refineries to harvest the molten metal output.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly38EnhancedTitle">Molten Springs</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly38EnhancedDescription">Refineries built over the planet's miraculous molten springs extract and refine valuable materials from the gouts of white-hot metal - although a few have been left pristine as spectacular (if dangerous) tourist destinations.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- I can't think how to fit Hyperium into this one, since it's a compound generally found in the oceans or atmosphere, not the crust. -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly39Title">Enhance Shattered Crust</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly39Description">Encourage a tourism industry to admire the breathtaking natural landscape.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly39EnhancedTitle">Shattered Crust</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly39EnhancedDescription">The surface of this planet is a riot of cliffs, chasms, ridges, and spikes, now traversed by soaring bridges, pierced with spectacular tunnels - and offering wonderful views to airships full of tourists.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly40Title">Enhance Komatiite Volcano</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly40Description">Study the planet's upper mantle, with an eye to artificial volcano formation.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly40EnhancedTitle">Komatiite Volcano</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly40EnhancedDescription">A thorough study of the local geology has revealed ways to trigger the formation of new komatiite volcanoes on demand. Industry leaders now regard the planet's upper mantle as a sort of vending machine: Insert explosives, receive magnesium.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly41Title">Enhance Propitious Seasons</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly41Description">Redesign your cities to take advantage of the seasonal variations.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly41EnhancedTitle">Propitious Seasons</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly41EnhancedDescription">The cities on this planet have been designed with the seasonal weather in mind, so no-one is too hot or too parched in the summer or too cold, wet, or depressed from lack of sunlight in the winter. </LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly42Title">Enhance Humeris Insidentes</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly42Description">Extract every last scrap of knowledge from the bunkers.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly42EnhancedTitle">Humeris Insidentes</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly42EnhancedDescription">Now that all of the knowledge banks and valuable archaeological finds from this planet's bunkers have been extracted, catalogued, stored and studied, the bunkers themselves - miles upon miles of subterranean tunnels - can be repurposed for your own data-centres and scientific archives.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- 43 is Poor Soil (Negative)  -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly43Title">Enhance Poor Soil</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly43Description">You've enriched the planet's soil to be able to support some crops - why stop there? You already have the infrastructure in place, so keep at it until you have an agricultural paradise.</LocalizationPair>
  
	<!-- 44 is High Gravity (Negative)  -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly44Title">Enhance High Gravity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly44Description">Crank up the Graviton Bleed Engine to higher power levels, and you might be able to get the gravity even lower! Or the planet might fall apart, but probably the other thing.</LocalizationPair>
  

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly45Title">Enhance Behemoth Song</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly45Description">Construct orbital habitats specially designed to channel the behemoth song.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly45EnhancedTitle">Behemoth Song</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly45EnhancedDescription">Orbital habitats have been constructed after the model of opera houses and amphitheatres, to allow everyone to experience the planet's haunting, ethereal song.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly46Title">Enhance Talking World</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly46Description">Study the mysterious radio transmissions.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly46EnhancedTitle">Talking World</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly46EnhancedDescription">Dedicated signal backtracing and code-cracking efforts have revealed the origin of the radio transmissions, although not their purpose - they appear to be nothing but a continual sequence of numbers, spoken in a recorded voice in a language of the Concrete Endless. Speculation abounds as to why.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly47Title">Enhance Fearful Symmetry</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly47Description">Study the symmetrical world, and try to work out how it got that way.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly47EnhancedTitle">Fearful Symmetry</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly47EnhancedDescription">Archeological studies have revealed the origin and purpose of this world's symmetry: It was once used by the Endless as a setting for planet-scale games of nation development, expansion, and war. The symmetrical structure allowed for both "players" to have identical prospects. Real life, of course, is neither fair nor balanced.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly48Title">Enhance High-Energy Plasmasphere</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly48Description">Construct additional pylons to stabilize the plasmasphere.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly48EnhancedTitle">High-Energy Plasmasphere</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly48EnhancedDescription">Massive pylons on the planet's surface stabilize and direct the natural plasmasphere, giving the entire world a shield equivalent to your strongest bunkers.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly49Title">Enhance Dust Halo</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly49Description">Study the dust halo, and try to work out if it really is sentient.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly49EnhancedTitle">Dust Halo</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly49EnhancedDescription">The question of the sentience of these vast fields of fluid, reactive Dust have been answered. Although not intelligent on their own, they are able to bond with a Dust-enhanced individual, and boost that person's awareness across the entire planet's surface.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- CRESCENT ANOMALIES -->
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly50Title">Enhance Artificial Life</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly50Description">Study the Crescent's curious affinity for artificial life.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly50EnhancedTitle">Artificial Life</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly50EnhancedDescription">While the source of this Crescent's beneficial effects on artificial life still remain a baffling mystery, we have decided that even if we can't understand it, we can certainly exploit it.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly51Title">Enhance Dust Accretor</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly51Description">Study the Crescent's ability to attract Dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly51EnhancedTitle">Dust Accretor</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly51EnhancedDescription">The Dust-attracting substances of this Crescent have been identified, and although we don't have enough of the raw materials to deploy them everywhere, we've made the best possible use of what we had and turned this Crescent into a veritable dust bonanza.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly52Title">Enhance Flickering Matter</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly52Description">Study the dematerializing matter within this Crescent.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly52EnhancedTitle">Flickering Matter</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly52EnhancedDescription">The intermittently dematerializing matter of this Crescent has been fully stabilized - but can still be made immaterial again on command. The industrial sectors of the Crescent now make use of machines once considered impossible, with parts moving through each other in an elegant automated ballet.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly53Title">Enhance Pseudo-Atmosphere</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomaly53Description">Study the crescent's atmospheric phenomena.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly53EnhancedTitle">Pseudo-Atmosphere</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly53EnhancedDescription">A pseudo-atmosphere appeared during the creation of this Crescent. The way light passes through it creates unique visuals, and we've finally found some less-easily-distracted scientists to help study the phenomenon.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- WONDER ANOMALIES -->
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder1Title">Enhance Dust Nebula</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder1Description">Study the dust nebula, and ensure it won't go back into "voracious self-replication" mode.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder1EnhancedTitle">Dust Nebula</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder1EnhancedDescription">For some time, we were justifiably cautious that the remains of the self-replicating Dust experiment here might reactivate and devour the entire system again. After extensive research, we are at last satisfied that the Dust here has been permanently rendered inert, is indistinguishable from normal Dust, and no longer needs to be kept separate from it.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder2Title">Enhance The Seventeen Thousand Islands Bridge</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder2Description">Develop the floating islands for new, luxurious, well-defended housing.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder2EnhancedTitle">The Seventeen Thousand Islands Bridge</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder2EnhancedDescription">An archipelago of natural islands that span the gap between planet surface and space, hanging in the darkness like glittering stepping stones, and now covered with some of the galaxy's most desirable (and best-defended) housing.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder3Title">Enhance The Fallen Gardens</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder3Description">Excavate the Fallen Gardens for ancient secrets of ship construction.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder3EnhancedTitle">The Fallen Gardens</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder3EnhancedDescription">Though the local religious sects were strongly against any "defilement" of the ancient structures, they were variously convinced, placated, discredited, or simply ignored. The treasures dug up from within the gardens proved to be well worth the effort, as ships built here can use lightweight hull materials and exotic drive cores not available anywhere else in the galaxy. Certain people still consider these ships to be holy relics.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder4Title">Enhance The Platform of Ys</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder4Description">Restore the military facilities of the spacedock platform.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder4EnhancedTitle">The Platform of Ys</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder4EnhancedDescription">The enormous spacedocks above the planet, once the greatest shipyard of the concrete Endless, have been partially restored. Although no longer able to build fleets, they provide ample staging posts for troops.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder5Title">Enhance Tree of Worlds</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder5Description">Study the Tree of Worlds and see if it can be replicated.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder5EnhancedTitle">Tree of Worlds</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder5EnhancedDescription">Your species' finest bioengineers have, at last, worked out how to duplicate this magnificent tree - admittedly, only with this planet's unique geology, and only on a much smaller scale. However, on this world at least, buildings and even entire cities can be grown rather than constructed.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder6Title">Enhance Tunneled Slipgates</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder6Description">Map the slipgate network and put it to good use.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder6EnhancedTitle">Tunneled Slipgates</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder6EnhancedDescription">A natural anomaly whose probable existence is less than zero, this series of natural quantum-linked transport gates create “tunnels” from the planets’ surfaces to various points in the star system. Now explored and mapped, the smaller and better-concealed slipgates can be used to covertly move troops.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- RUIN ANOMALIES - REDUCED -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeTitle">Clean Debris Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeDescription">Clean up the orbital debris around this planet.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeReducedTitle">Large Debris Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeReducedDescription">The site of a major engagement between warring empires, the space surrounding this system took years to sweep clear of dangerous debris.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumTitle">Clean Debris Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumDescription">Clean up the orbital debris around this planet.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumReducedTitle">Medium Debris Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumReducedDescription">The site of an engagement between enemy fleets, the space surrounding this system took months to sweep clear of dangerous debris.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallTitle">Clean Debris Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallDescription">Clean up the orbital debris around this planet.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallReducedTitle">Small Debris Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallReducedDescription">Little reminder of the previous skirmish remains, even the orbital debris is no longer a nuisance.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionTitle">Clean Pre-galactic Architecture</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionDescription">Clean up what remains of your battles with the former civilization on this world.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionReducedTitle">Pre-galactic Architecture</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionReducedDescription">A minor civilization that resisted assimilation was conquered here, but only memorials remain.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeTitle">Clean Pirate Stronghold</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeDescription">Prosecute any remaining pirates and deal with the mess they left behind.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeReducedTitle">Gutted Pirate Stronghold</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeReducedDescription">A thriving pirate colony was laid to waste here, resulting in massive devastation and debris.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumTitle">Clean Pirate Lair</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumDescription">Prosecute any remaining pirates and deal with the mess they left behind.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumReducedTitle">Gutted Pirate Lair</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumReducedDescription">There was once a pirate hideout here, but only ruins and debris remain.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallTitle">Clean Pirate Hideout</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallDescription">Prosecute any remaining pirates and deal with the mess they left behind.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallReducedTitle">Gutted Pirate Hideout</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallReducedDescription">A small band of pirates once held this place, but they were driven out and only some debris remains.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeTitle">Clean Apocalyptic Landscape</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeDescription">Clean up the battlefields of this war-torn world.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeReducedTitle">Apocalyptic Landscape</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeReducedDescription">An enormous ground battle occurred here, and the planet will forever show the horrific scars.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumTitle">Clean Devastation</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumDescription">Clean up the battlefields of this war-torn world.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumReducedTitle">Devastation</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumReducedDescription">A ground battle took place here, and the planet is only slowly recovering.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallTitle">Clean Trenches</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReducePlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallDescription">Clean up the battlefields of this war-torn world.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallReducedTitle">Trenches</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallReducedDescription">A minor engagement occurred here, but the evidence of battle is already disappearing.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- RUIN ANOMALIES - ENHANCED -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeTitle">Enhance Debris Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeDescription">Survey the remains of the orbital debris around this planet.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeEnhancedTitle">Large Debris Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeEnhancedDescription">The site of a major engagement between warring empires, now swept clear of dangerous orbital debris. It also provided a wealth of survey data that you used to enhance locally-built ships.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumTitle">Enhance Debris Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumDescription">Survey the remains of the orbital debris around this planet.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumEnhancedTitle">Medium Debris Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumEnhancedDescription">The site of an engagement between enemy fleets, now swept clear of dangerous orbital debris. It also provided some helpful survey data that you used to enhance locally-built ships.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallTitle">Enhance Debris Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallDescription">Survey the remains of the orbital debris around this planet.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallEnhancedTitle">Small Debris Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallEnhancedDescription">A reminder of a previous skirmish, now swept clear of dangerous orbital debris. It also provided a smidgin of data that you used to enhance locally-built ships.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionTitle">Enhance Pre-galactic Architecture</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionDescription">Study the remains of the minor civilization on this world.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionEnhancedTitle">Pre-galactic Architecture</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionEnhancedDescription">A minor civilization that resisted assimilation was conquered here, and while no trace of the battles remain, we have since learned better ways of dealing with foreign species.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeTitle">Enhance Pirate Stronghold</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeDescription">Repurpose the pirate technology for your own use.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeEnhancedTitle">Gutted Pirate Stronghold</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeEnhancedDescription">A thriving pirate colony was laid to waste here. They left behind heavy surface-to-orbit particle cannons that have now been repaired for your own use.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumTitle">Enhance Pirate Lair</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumDescription">Repurpose the pirate technology for your own use.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumEnhancedTitle">Gutted Pirate Lair</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumEnhancedDescription">There was once a pirate hideout here. They left behind laser installations that have now been repaired for your own use.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallTitle">Enhance Pirate Hideout</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallDescription">Repurpose the pirate technology for your own use.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallEnhancedTitle">Gutted Pirate Hideout</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallEnhancedDescription">A small band of pirates once held this place. They left behind point defence guns that have now been repaired for your own use.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeTitle">Enhance Apocalyptic Landscape</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeDescription">Repair the fortifications that still remain on this world's battlefields.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeEnhancedTitle">Apocalyptic Landscape</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeEnhancedDescription">An enormous ground battle occurred here, and your own military has made good use of the miles of tunnels and bunkers.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumTitle">Enhance Devastation</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumDescription">Repair the fortifications that still remain on this world's battlefields.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumEnhancedTitle">Devastation</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumEnhancedDescription">A ground battle took place here, and your own military has made good use of the remaining fortifications.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallTitle">Enhance Trenches</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToEnhancePlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallDescription">Repair the fortifications that still remain on this world's battlefields.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallEnhancedTitle">Trenches</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallEnhancedDescription">A minor engagement occurred here, and your own military has made good use of the trenches and craters.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- MIXED & NEGATIVE - REDUCED -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly10Title">Reduce Ice-10</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly10Description">Develop construction materials that can build stable roads over the Ice-10 fields.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly10ReducedTitle">Ice-10</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly10ReducedDescription">A rare form of ice that is caused by water crystallizing under high pressures, Ice-10 is interesting for its thermodynamic properties. A concerted effort by the planet's engineers has led to a lessening of its negative effects.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly11Title">Reduce Permanent Monsoon</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly11Description">Begin terraforming efforts to bring the monsoon under control.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly11ReducedTitle">Permanent Monsoon</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly11ReducedDescription">Once a very wet and very difficult environment, a concerted effort to partially terraform the planet has lessened the intensity of the winds and storms.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly12Title">Reduce Metallic Waters</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly12Description">Develop artificial soils that can mitigate this planet's strange surface conditions.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly12ReducedTitle">Metallic Waters</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly12ReducedDescription">Almost dirt-free, the hard, gleaming surface of this planet used to make agriculture difficult and potentially poisonous. Recent improvements in soil development, however, have eased the problem.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly13Title">Reduce Aurora Waves</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly13Description">Deploy magnetic shielding to reduce the disruptive effects of the aurora waves.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly13ReducedTitle">Aurora Waves</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly13ReducedDescription">The gleaming, multi-colored auroras that once caused such headaches have been partially tamed by magnetic shielding. Fortunately, their beauty remains even though their negative effects have been reduced.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly15Title">Reduce Psychoactive Air</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly15Description">Spray fine crystals into the atmosphere to encourage heavy rainfall and sweep the psychoactive compounds out of the air.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly15ReducedTitle">Psychoactive Air</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly15ReducedDescription">With an atmosphere that was once saturated by complex chemical compounds, life on this planet was challenging. Application of terraforming technologies, however, has rendered the effects of the air less intense.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly16Title">Reduce Geothermic Activity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly16Description">Set up the first wave of gravity control stations to get the planet's unpredictable mantle under control.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly16ReducedTitle">Geothermic Activity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly16ReducedDescription">Applying enormous amounts of energy and grappling with gravitational alterations, the previously uncontrollable geothermic activity of the planet is now somewhat less intense.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly17Title">Reduce Seismic Activity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly17Description">Set up the first wave of gravity control stations to get the planet's unpredictable mantle under control.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly17ReducedTitle">Seismic Activity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly17ReducedDescription">By manipulating the magnetic core, stabilizing continental drift, and improving construction techniques, the problems in daily life caused by seismic activity have been notably reduced.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly18Title">Reduce Long Season</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly18Description">Employ a team of climate scientists, architects, and agricultural specialists to make life on this planet more pleasant.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly18ReducedTitle">Long Season</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly18ReducedDescription">While the long orbital ellipse remains a fact of life, the application of terraforming sciences, advanced architecture, and improved agriculture has changed it from a health risk into a quaint tourist adventure.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly19Title">Reduce Meteor Strikes</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly19Description">Deploy so-called "killer satellites" to shoot down meteors before they hit.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly19ReducedTitle">Meteor Strikes</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly19ReducedDescription">For the first time in the history of the universe, the phrase "killer satellites" actually has a practical meaning. Thanks to cheap and robust sources of energy and heavily shielded orbitals, major meteor threats are neutralized high in the atmosphere.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly20Title">Reduce Polar Tempests</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly20Description">Employ a team of climate scientists, architects, and cold-weather survival experts to make life on this planet more pleasant.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly20ReducedTitle">Polar Tempests</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly20ReducedDescription">Controlled global warming, advanced thermo-efficient architecture, and really warm parkas have greatly lessened the negative effects of this anomaly.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly21Title">Reduce Magnetic Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly21Description">Send a crack science team to see if they can develop a solution to the magnetic field problems.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly21ReducedTitle">Strong Magnetic Field</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly21ReducedDescription">Once directed non-baryonic magnetic flux technology was reduced to handheld size, the negative impacts of this anomaly were greatly reduced.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly22Title">Reduce Kessler Syndrome</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly22Description">Begin an unglamorous and expensive programme to sweep the debris out of orbit.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly22ReducedTitle">Kessler Syndrome</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly22ReducedDescription">Though it took time, patience, and very large nets, much of the orbital debris that circulated the planet has been removed or dumped planetside for recycling.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly23Title">Reduce Acid Rain</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly23Description">Deploy new, acid-resistant materials for use in construction - and see if you can do something about the fumaroles, too.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly23ReducedTitle">Acid Rain</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly23ReducedDescription">Partially by reducing the effects of the fumaroles and partially by hardening the infrastructure, many of the problems caused by this anomaly have been alleviated.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly24Title">Reduce Irradiation</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly24Description">Set up massive chemical plants to reinforce the planet's ozone layer.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly24ReducedTitle">Irradiated</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly24ReducedDescription">By developing and improving the ozone layer and atmosphere while better insulating construction, a large part of the dangerous effects of this radiation has been removed.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly28Title">Reduce Hostile Fauna</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly28Description">Have your top ecologists work on a programme of taming the local wildlife.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly28ReducedTitle">Docile Fauna</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly28ReducedDescription">While the beasts of this planet were first described as "giant," "primal," and "impressive," these days the adjectives would tend to "controlled," "manageable," and "delicious."</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly39Title">Reduce Shattered Crust</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly39Description">Fund a vast programme of engineering projects to give this planet a functioning transportation network despite the landscape.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly39ReducedTitle">Tunneled Crust</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly39ReducedDescription">Though the surface of this planet remains rough, a few engineering projects involving viaducts and tunnels have rendered this problem unimportant. Fortunately, the landscape remains impressive.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly43Title">Reduce Poor Soil</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly43Description">Fund extensive deployment of new fertilizer factories.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly43ReducedTitle">Arable Soil</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly43ReducedDescription">The soil of this planet, once sterile and barren, is now much richer in the organic life necessary for agriculture.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly44Title">Reduce High Gravity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly44Description">Overrule the population's objection to "insane, untested science" and "playing god", and power up the Graviton Bleed Engine already.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly44ReducedTitle">Acceptable Gravity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly44ReducedDescription">By the simple and straightforward process of bleeding excess gravitons across hyperdimensions into a parallel universe, the previously extreme gravity of the planet has been somewhat reduced.</LocalizationPair>

<!-- Crescent anomalies -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly52Title">Reduce Flickering Matter</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly52Description">Study the flickering matter, and see if its dematerialization is predictable.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly52ReducedTitle">Flickering Matter</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly52ReducedDescription">The matter still tends to flicker, but it is now possible to predict these changes rather accurately. No more spontaneous disappearance of ships from construction hangars.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly53Title">Reduce Pseudo-Atmosphere</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly53Description">Set up and promote a research group to study the pseudo-atmosphere.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly53ReducedTitle">Pseudo-Atmosphere</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly53ReducedDescription">All it took was encouraging the study of the luminous phenomena of this pseudo-atmosphere for the inhabitants of this Crescent to regain their interest in science.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly54Title">Reduce Low-Quality Foundations</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly54Description">Begin the long and unglamorous process of shoring up the crescent's foundations.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly54ReducedTitle">Low-Quality Foundations</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly54ReducedDescription">After long and tedious efforts, every defect in the Crescent has been fixed. These all too frequent malfunctions are now just a bad memory.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly55Title">Reduce Uninhabitable Area</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ToReduceAnomaly55Description">Focus on reworking the crescent's structure to restore habitability.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly55ReducedTitle">Uninhabitable Area</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly55ReducedDescription">The uninhabitable section of the Crescent has finally been reworked, everything is back to normal. If the Crescents were something normal in the first place.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Empire Improvement -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementAnomalyReduction1EffectOverride">Allows Anomaly Reduction

Anomaly Reduction lets you remove the negative effects of a Negative Anomaly</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementAnomalyReduction2EffectOverride">Allows Anomalies Enhancement

Anomaly Enhancement lets you increase the positive effects of a Positive Anomaly</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Political Event -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationPoliticalEventEnhancedAnomalyTitle">Anomaly Enhanced</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Failure Message -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FailureEnhancementEcologistsDescription">Anomaly Enhancement requires the [ecologistColored] #B0C65D#Ecologists#REVERT# to be the Primary Political Party</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Reduction dropdown tooltip -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetReduceAnomalyButtonDescription">Click to select an anomaly improvement for this planet</LocalizationPair>
</Datatable>