<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MinorFactionQuest16-Choice01Objective">Raise your [militaristColored] #B82738#Militarist#REVERT# support to at least 15% in $Amount01Name Systems</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Defensive Trait -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipStatBonus2DefensiveTitle">Defensive</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipStatBonus2DefensiveDescription">+10% Ship Health, +10% Shield Capacity and +10% Defense on Plating and Shields</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Protector Trait -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipStatBonus2ProtectorTitle">Protector</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipStatBonus2ProtectorDescription">+20% Ship Health, +20% Shield Capacity and +20% Defense on Plating and Shields</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Morale Effect-->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%MoraleBonusEvasionTitle">Evasion on Fleet</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Targeting Explanations -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipRoleSmallAttackerDescription">The role of this ship is to inflict massive damage on the enemy.
Primary targets: Protector and then Coordinator ships
Secondary targets: Carrier ships</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipRoleMediumAttackerDescription">The role of this ship is to inflict massive damage on the enemy.
Primary targets: Protector and then Coordinator ships
Secondary targets: Carrier ships</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipRoleSmallSupportDescription">The role of this ship is to protect other ships in battle.
Primary targets: Attacker and then Hunter ships
Secondary targets: Protector and Coordinator ships</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipRoleMediumSupportDescription">The role of this ship is to protect or assist other ships in battle.
Primary targets: Attacker and Hunter ships
Secondary targets: Protector and Coordinator ships</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportJammer1Strategic3Description">Generating reflective and signal-lensing chaff, ships equipped with these jamming modules will be difficult to target and thus will be hit less often.
When used on military ships, ensures the ship is targeted last.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportJammer2Strategic5Description">Orichalcix 's extreme density can cause local distortions to gravity and space. These modules take advantage of this effect, causing enemy weapons to be less likely to target and hit equipped ships.
When used on any ship, ensures the ship is targeted last.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportBait1Strategic4Description">Due to its high energy output, the sub-quantic properties of Antimatter can be used to warp targeting signals and weapons' fire. The result is that a ship equipped with these modules will tend to be targeted more often.
When used, ensures your military ship is targeted first.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportBait2Strategic6Description">Using wave and energy rather than material properties, quadrinix lensing systems are even more effective than their adamantian counterparts. These modules extruded from quadrinix foundries will cause enemy fleets to fire more often on these ships.
When used, ensures any ship is targeted first.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipRoleHeroDescription">This type of ship is bound to a Hero.  All [commandPoint] (Command Points) cost are cancelled. Hero ships are targeted by enemy ships as if they are Attacker class.
Primary targets: Medium sized ships
Secondary targets: Large sized ships</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipRoleBattleshipDescription">Juggernauts are targeted first by military ships.
The Juggernaut is the biggest and strongest ship in the galaxy. It can be embedded in fleets and can be further upgraded, either by having more slots, or by unlocking the Ion Wave, a powerful ability which damages all fleets present on the node.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%ShipRoleJuggernautDescription">Behemoths are targeted first by military ships.
Behemoth roles vary depending on the Modules you equip them with. They can focus on economic, scientific, or military capacities.</LocalizationPair>
</Datatable>