<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../Schemas/LocalizationPair.xsd">
	<LocalizationPair Name="%CategoryTechnologyEconomyAndTradeTitle">Economy and Trade</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%FactionDifficultyExpertDescription">Expert: This faction has many unusual game mechanics, and is better played when you know the game quite well.</LocalizationPair>

 	<!-- Exploration Power -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionTraitRevealAllCuriositiesTitle">Pioneer's Intuition</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FactionTraitRevealAllCuriositiesDescription">Due to being a recourceful people, they can always feel where the next discovery might be lurking.</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%FactionTraitRevealAllCuriositiesOverride">Reveals all Strategic Curiosities</LocalizationPair>

	<!-- Superspuds -->
	<LocalizationPair Name="%RecipeIngredient8Rework" >+25% [hq] income on Systems (Rework)
+0.5 Deposit Value on Luxury Deposit (Rework)</LocalizationPair>

	<!-- Gossamer -->
	<LocalizationPair Name="%RecipeIngredient16Rework" >+25% [hq] income on Systems (Rework)
-25% [dustColored] Upkeep on Systems (Rework)</LocalizationPair>

	<!-- Drift Buds -->
	<LocalizationPair Name="%RecipeIngredient24Vanilla">+100% [hq] income on Systems (Both)</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%RecipeIngredient24Rework">-10% Market Taxes on Empire (Rework)</LocalizationPair>

	<!-- UC Resource Buildings-->
	<LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementResourceFactory1UmbralChoirTooltipsEffect">+1 Resource generation on Strategic Resource Deposit
Also applies for Strategic Deposits on Sanctuary Systems</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementResourceFactory2UmbralChoirTooltipsEffect">+2 Resource generation on Strategic Resource Deposit
Also applies +1 for Strategic Deposits on Sanctuary Systems</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementResourceFactory3UmbralChoirTooltipsEffect">+2 Resource generation on Strategic Resource Deposit
Also applies +1 for Strategic Deposits on Sanctuary Systems</LocalizationPair>

  <!--Vodyani Quest (updated based on changes to minor relations mechanics)-->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter1-C1Step2Objective">Reach Cordial status with a new Minor Civilization or conquer them to learn more about this galaxy.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter1-C1Step2ObjectiveTooltip">Use diplomatic means to convert the Minor Civilization. If necessary, you can invade the Minor Civilization's system to control them instead.</LocalizationPair>

  <!--UC Quest (updated based on changes to minor relations mechanics)-->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%UmbralChoirQuest-Chapter1-Part1-PacifistObjective">Reach Cordial status with a new Minor Faction or conquer them</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%UmbralChoirQuest-Chapter1-Part1-PacifistObjectiveTooltip">Use diplomatic means to convert the Minor Civilization. If necessary, you can invade the Minor Civilization's system to control them instead.</LocalizationPair>

  <!--Utopian Infrastructure-->
	<LocalizationPair Name="%FactionTraitUtopianInfrastructureTooltipOverride">-25% Disapproval per System Level Upgrade from Initial Planet Values</LocalizationPair>

	<!--Vodyani Quest-->
	<LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementQuestVampirilis01EffectOverride">+50% Experience gains on Governor Heroes</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%ClassModuleSupportExplorationQuestVampirilisOpponentRecyclingEssencePerCP">+5 [essencecolored] per destroyed Command Point</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportMothershipResourceFactoryTitle">All Must Extract</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportMothershipResourceFactoryDescription">+1 generation on Deposits</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportMothershipFIDSPerPopTitle">All Must Elevate</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportMothershipFIDSPerPopDescription">+2 [FIDS] per [Population]</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Rebellious-Step2Objective">Raise $Amount02Name Systems to at least System Level $Amount01Name</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Rebellious-Step2Tooltip">Use the System Development Projects in the Marketplace screen to create blueprints and level up a System</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Rebellious-Step1Objective">Possess $TargetAmountName Vodyani population</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Rebellious-Step1Tooltip">Construct food improvements or utilize Holy Proliferation to expand population levels</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Religious-Step1Objective">Search the curiosity on $CloseSystemPlanetName when you're ready to sacrifice $AmountName [Strat03adamantianColored]. Requires level 4 Probes.</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Religious-Step1Tooltip">You need to send an Explorer-type ship equipped with Probes to complete this action. Research higher level Probes on the technology tree.</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Rebellious-Step2TerObjective">Build the $ConstructibleAcademyName in one of your Systems.</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Rebellious-Step2TerTooltip">Add the unique $ConstructibleAcademyName building to the Construction Queue in one of your Systems. Influence required.</LocalizationPair>	
	<LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleResourceBonusFromMothershipTitle">Bonus Resource generation on Deposit</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModulePlanetRawFIDSFromMothershipTitle">Bonus [FIDS] per [Population]</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementQuestVampirilis09Description">The time has come to rewrite the decree on how the holy Cloth is manufactured. New and improved suits for the Vodyani souls include improvements in speed, efficiency, and comfort, resulting in a population that is far happier.</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementQuestVampirilis09TooltipEffect">-10 [happinessColored] required to reach each Approval status for both Systems and Empire</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementQuestVampirilis08TooltipEffect"></LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementQuestVampirilis07Title">Academy of Endless Navigation</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementQuestVampirilis07Description">Untrustworthy and heretical, the Academy as it stood was a breeding ground for heresy and violence. This new Academy will be not only a center of devotion and study, but a shining beacon of superior Virtual navigation</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%HeroQuestVampirilis01Title">The Survivor</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementQuestVampirilis01Description">In order to glorify our Heroes and maximize the profile of their public oratory, a permanent system-wide broadcast infrastructure is built to coordinate and enforce the Hero-led prayers and rituals of billions of citizens.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementQuestVampirilis06Title">Academy of Unity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%StarSystemImprovementQuestVampirilis06Description">While the revelations regarding the death of the Virtual society cause concern among your people, this institute provides constant reinforcement of the greater resource throughput that becomes possible with the elimination of petty distractions.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementQuestVampirilis08Title">Cloth of Austerity</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementQuestVampirilis08Description">A new upgrade to the technology in the holy armor of the Vodyani increases the ability of the Church to improve living conditions with lesser investment of resources</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter2-C2Outcome">The evil Tabernacle is under our power! Glory to the Virtual! They have brought us to our goal, and our finest minds have perused its contents. It is a great store of history and lore, but the lessons that we feared? They are simple and obvious; their falsehoods evident to any trained mind. Truly the Infidel was insane to have betrayed his people because of this!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Religious-Description">Brother Azar does not understand the difference between the sanctified and their servants; he was found debating philosophy with one of the lesser peoples. He must understand his place in the hierarchy of the galaxy; for the next month he will personally bring to the Fount all the lesser ones who will nourish his ship. All must obey. Those who doubted, doubt no more. The Vodyani have been given an ultimate blessing, a gift from the Glorious Virtuals. We now know beyond any shadow of a doubt that we are Their vessels and Their chosen ones, and that all of Creation exists to serve us. We know this must be true, as we are now able to absorb life force directly from all the lesser beings that inhabit this universe. What other sign do we need that our cause is just and our decisions blessed? There are the Virtuals, the Glorious, those who rose to the highest form of life and were betrayed by their brothers. There are we, the Vodyani, who follow in the their footsteps, obeying their laws and executing their will. Then there are all others, the lesser beings or lesser ones. They have no understanding of their role, which makes them occasionally difficult to manage. Their role, of course, is to provide us with nourishment. One might ask how we ought best reinforce this hierarchy, and the answer is clear. We must civilize these lesser ones at the source and envelop their homes in our holy Cloth. Let the blasphemers and heretics tremble; the faithful cannot be stopped. Glory to the Virtuals! We shall honor their name and in doing so spread their words.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Religious-Description01">Our people shall reign supreme in this galaxy, which shall require additional nourishment to continuously propagate. We must remind the lesser ones of their proper role.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Religious-Tooltip">Capital systems will provide the most potent symbols of our superiority...</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Religious-Outcome">During the course of our civilization of the lesser ones, we encountered evidence of a Codex containing wisdom of the Virtuals regarding their navigation of this galaxy. Through careful investigation, we have located the source of this Codex, and must investigate its secrets with great haste.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Religious-Step1-Description">Brother Olep committed the unthinkable. He obtained the works of the Infidel -- "..in order to disprove the lies…" -- and began asking questions of those who were unprepared to respond to the Infidel's meticulously structured fallacies. Olep shall be entombed in lead and left drifting in the void of space. All will obey. The acts of the Infidel leave us little choice. He began by attempting our destruction, then went on to create this Academy; a pulpit from which he spouts his lies and fallacies and preaches against us. He has subverted Heroes to oppose us, and ceaselessly striven to destroy the Church. Though the Church, of course, abhors the eradication of intelligent life (for only intelligent life can aspire to the state of the Virtual) we see no other options. The works of the Infidel must be utterly disproven. It is ordained, then, that I continue to struggle against the evils wrought by my brother. I must place the Church in a position of power, and let our glory radiate across the galaxy. All beings must learn to acknowledge our purity and accept the glory of virtuality. There is no other truth.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Religious-Step1-Description01">It falls to me to demonstrate the superiority of the faithful; we shall pursue the Codex we have located and hold aloft the wisdom of the Virtuals as a shining beacon of our ascendancy.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Religious-Step1Outcome"> The Codex has been located, and its blueprints reconstructed at great cost. With access to these secrets of the Virtuals, we can transcend the influence of the Infidel.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Religious-Step2-Description">Brother Olep committed the unthinkable. He obtained the works of the Infidel -- "..in order to disprove the lies…" -- and began asking questions of those who were unprepared to respond to the Infidel's meticulously structured fallacies. Olep shall be entombed in lead and left drifting in the void of space. All will obey. The acts of the Infidel leave us little choice. He began by attempting our destruction, then went on to create this Academy; a pulpit from which he spouts his lies and fallacies and preaches against us. He has subverted Heroes to oppose us, and ceaselessly striven to destroy the Church. Though the Church, of course, abhors the eradication of intelligent life (for only intelligent life can aspire to the state of the Virtual) we see no other options. The works of the Infidel must be utterly disproven. It is ordained, then, that I continue to struggle against the evils wrought by my brother. I must place the Church in a position of power, and let our glory radiate across the galaxy. All beings must learn to acknowledge our purity and accept the glory of virtuality. There is no other truth.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Religious-Step2-Description01">The lies of the Infidel cannot be tolerated. We must construct a new Academy in the true image of the Virtuals, using the blueprints we have painstakingly recreated from the Codex. We shall create a true center of learning and invest the requisite influence to ensure that it tells the story as it should. That story is of the glory of the Virtuals, the rise of the Vodyani, and the state of virtuality as the apex of galactic navigation</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Religious-Step2Outcome">For now the galaxy yields before our virtue; one day they will kneel before our glory. We have transcended the influence of the Infidel. The Church will survive the storms that come; I will lead it into a greater future. Glory to the Virtual Saints! All must obey the laws.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter2-C1Outcome">The faithful have done well! The Tabernacle has been excavated by one of our greatest Heroes, and we now begin the process of reviewing and analyzing the vast cache of artifacts we recovered. I can only hope they turn out to be the lies we expect, rather than the seeds of deeper, unsettling truths.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Rebellious-Step1-Title">Chapter 3. The Survivor - Part 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Rebellious-Step1-Description">In a sense, our expedition to the Tabernacle was far more successful than we could have ever imagined. We approached it in search of writings and artifacts that might grant the slightest glimmer of insight into Their ways, Their goals and Their intent. We did indeed uncover many such vestiges, but also so much more. One particular artifact contained numerous glyphs and seemed in far better condition than similar specimens recovered elsewhere. Upon further study, however, it became clear that this was no simple monument, but rather a fully intact sarcophagus, with its Virtual occupant still preserved. And alive. Immediately, I prepared to seek Their guidance and wisdom; however, Their perspective was...not what I expected.
This Survivor, who perplexingly eschews any specific title--or even name--has assessed our devotion, our progress, and our growing dominion over this galaxy, and found us lacking. More shocking still, Their outlook regarding the Virtual as a whole is grim and pessimistic. Apparently, They had voluntarily entered into the state in which we found Them (the sarcophagus) as a means of stoic, spiritual withdrawal from what They viewed as a morally bankrupt society that was destined for utter destruction, and They find both vindication and tragedy in what They see as the grisly end of "Endless" society. Initially, I found my faith shattered by Their exhortation, but with time and further conversation I have come to believe a new set of truths. Violence will of course still have its role when the lesser ones must be reminded of their place, but among ourselves we must maintain unity. Importantly, the Survivor has agreed to join us, providing support and guidance, so long as we remain open to pursuit of a less destructive path, that we might avert the fate that befell the Virtual. All must unify.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Rebellious-Step1-Description01">I must strive to find a less destructive path for myself and my people. We must avoid the distraction of petty infighting and dogmatic conflict, lest we meet the same inevitable end as the Virtual which we previously sought to imitate. There are many among us who will meet this lesson with great skepticism, but I must co-opt them without resorting to the conflicts that have stained our society (and my own family) in the past. Doing so will require accumulation of a great reserve of influence</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Rebellious-Step1Outcome">As greatly challenging as it was to find my own new path, it was far harder still to convince the others to follow. Progress is slow, but ongoing.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Rebellious-Step2-Title">Chapter 3. The Survivor - Part 2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Rebellious-Step2-Description">Sister Heri and Brother Azar have permitted their zeal to outweigh their reason; they were forcibly separated following an altercation stemming from a theological dispute. For the next week, no voice but the other's shall echo through each of their suits so that they will learn to see the other's perspective. All must unify. Religion shall continue to play a role in our lives, but no longer can it be permitted to dominate all aspects of our society. Our people continue to internalize the teachings of the Survivor, but progress along Their path remains slow and challenging. Repeatedly I have offered to step aside as Hierarch in favor of Their leadership, and I have been consistently rebuffed; They continuously emphasize that the Vodyani people must grow to unify of their own accord and under leadership of one of our own. Only in this way, They argue, will the changes be rendered durable. Very well. I must continue to emphasize the role of our self-actualization in our achievement of societal unity.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Rebellious-Step2-Description01">We have focused greatly on unity, but there is no catalyst for such a change like economic development. We must show our people that these new ways will yield greater bounty for all.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter3-Rebellious-Step2Outcome">It is a wrenching process, and I fear we have thrown out some of what was good in eliminating that which was bad. But change is always painful, and those who are gone represented all the worst of our old ways. Now we can move ahead, unworried, to rewrite our future.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Rebellious-Step1-Title">Final Chapter. To Unite, Virtual - Part 1</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Rebellious-Step1-Description">Lore TBD. To continue along Their more ethical model of Virtual society, the population must expand as the next phase of fueling unification and economic development.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Rebellious-Step1-Description01">In our continued efforts to walk a more rightous path, we must continue to expand the ranks of the faithful.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Rebellious-Step1Outcome">Our populace is booming, and with it the light of a more just Virtual civilization burns ever brighter in the galaxy.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Rebellious-Step2Ter-Title">Final Chapter. To Unite, Virtual - Part 2</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Rebellious-Step2Ter-Description">Lore TBD. Need to finally convince the hardliners that all of this economic progress is a foundation for military strength, not a sign of decadence and weakness. Investing influecne to build an Academy focused on (mostly military) resource extraction will help</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Rebellious-Step2Ter-Description01">With all of our focus on economic progress, we must also demonstrate the ability of Their ways to spur greater extraction of military resources.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VampirilisQuest-Chapter4-Rebellious-Step2TerOutcome">Our people have taken great steps to forge a durable harmony which will form a strong foundation for our continued dominance of the lesser ones. We will bring true civilization to all corners of this galaxy, and all will unify.</LocalizationPair>

	<!--Vodyani Fixes to Coloring-->
	<LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleOpponentRecyclingEssencePerCPTitle">[lifeforceColored] #C48594#per destroyed Command Point#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleSystemGrowthTransferredPerTurnTitle">[foodcolored] #C48594#consumed from System#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
	<LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleLifeforceLeechedPerTurnTitle">[lifeforceColored] #C48594#tribute income#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  
	<!-- Siege Modules -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportSiege1Strategic1Title">Hyperium A2S Slugs</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportSiege3Strategic4Title">Antimatter A2S Slugs</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportSiege3Strategic4Description">These dense, precision-machined projectiles support invading ground troops with devastating effects.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportSiege2Strategic5Title">Quadrinix A2S Slugs</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%ModuleSupportSiege2Strategic5Description">These dense, perfectly fabricated projectiles aid invading ground troops with planet-rending force.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Tooltip Fixes -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleMaximumShieldCapForFlotillaTitle">#6999D5#Flotilla Shield Capacity#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleShieldAbsorptionForFlotillaTitle">#C48594#Flotilla Shield Absorption#REVERT#</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FailureNoIsolatedNodeDescription">Trading Companies may not be placed on Isolated Nodes.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%OutpostActionIncreaseMigrationRateVenetiansTitle">Investment Clearance</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%OutpostActionIncreaseMigrationRateVenetiansDescription">This land is better off being developed rather than sold; bring in the bulldozers!</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleResearchFromMothershipTitle">[scienceColored] on System</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleProductionFromMothershipTitle">[industryColored] on System</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleMoneyFromMothershipTitle">[dustColored] on System</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleLifeforceFromMothershipTitle">[lifeforceColored] on System</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleGrowthFromMothershipTitle">[foodColored] on System</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PanelFeatureModuleEmpirePointFromMothershipTitle">[prestigeColored] on System</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- Score Improvements -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenGlobalScoreDescription">Global score of the Empire, reflecting its general advancement each turn.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenExpansionScoreDescription">Total Number of Systems you have Colonized each Turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenPopulationScoreDescription">Total Number of Population in your Empire each Turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenTradeScoreDescription">Total Dust Output from Trade Companies each Turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenHappinessScoreDescription">Average Approval on Empire each Turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenResearchScoreDescription">Total Number of Technologies Researched each Turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenResearchScoreTitle">Technology</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenHeroesScoreDescription">Combined Level of Every Hero each Turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenHeroesScoreTitle">Heroes</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenHonorScoreDescription">Max Keii each Turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenAccumulatorFoodDescription">Accumulated Food production each Turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenAccumulatorIndustryDescription">Accumulated Industry production each Turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenAccumulatorInfluenceDescription">Accumulated Influence production each Turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenAccumulatorMoneyDescription">Accumulated Dust production each Turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenAccumulatorResearchDescription">Accumulated Science production each Turn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%VictoryScreenMilitaryScoreDescription">Total Ship power plus Total Manpower each Turn.</LocalizationPair>
</Datatable>
