<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">

  <!-- <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyEndlessWonder1EnhancedTitle">Husk of Knowledge (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair> -->
  <!-- <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyEndlessWonder1EnhancedDescription">Auriga housed the greatest site for the study of xenobiology ever created by the genius of the Endless. A towering achievement of industry and science, the surface and crust of the planet were a warren of laboratories, biospheres, and research centers. When the bombs fell during the Dust Wars, this enormous installation became the greatest expanse of ruins - and store of lost knowledge - in the known galaxy. Should the laboratories ever be repaired and the data recovered, the scientific benefit would be unimaginable.</LocalizationPair> -->
  <!-- <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyEndlessWonder2EnhancedTitle">Spotora's Sanctum (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair> -->
  <!-- <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyEndlessWonder2EnhancedDescription">Also known as the Icarael's Watch, this is the one laboratory in all of the Endless-controlled galaxy that had the best claim to the discovery of the science of virtualization. Spotora Ortamm and her team are credited with the first consistent, replicable method for the virtualization of a sentient mind; the notes and equipment have enormous value in spite of their age.</LocalizationPair> -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly01EnhancedTitle">Garden of Eden (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly01EnhancedDescription">Lush and pleasant, with a single year-round season of moderate temperatures, life is good on this planet. Everyone benefits from its natural wealth: Residents, tourists, businessmen, and scientists.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly02EnhancedTitle">Dust Ruins (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly02EnhancedDescription">Many ruins from the time of the Endless were Dust-enhanced structures or traditional buildings that preceded the Dust era. On very rare occasions, however, one can find entire structures built uniquely from this valuable resource.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly03EnhancedTitle">Friendly Locals (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly03EnhancedDescription">Integrating the planet's native people and culture into their society from the start, and acting as guests rather than colonizers, this world's population have become more accepting of others. The multicultural society here is a wonderful working environment for all the myriad species of your empire.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly04EnhancedTitle">Rich Soil (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly04EnhancedDescription">The soil of this planet is so rich in bacteria and nutrients, and so good at promoting plant growth, that it's actually profitable to mine dirt and ship it to other planets in the system.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly05EnhancedTitle">Mineral Rich (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly05EnhancedDescription">The planet's bountiful crust has been a blessing for the economy, once the initial lawless free-for-all was reined in. Now, land deeds are correctly recorded, deep-mining operations appropriately regulated, and even most of the original pollution has been cleaned up.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly06EnhancedTitle">Hadopelagic Life (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly06EnhancedDescription">It took a lot of doing, given the frankly murderous pressures involved, but your empire succeeded in constructing an ultra-deep-sea laboratory to study this planet's unique life-forms. People being as they are, it was soon followed by the galaxy's deepest underwater hotel, a lunatic endeavor that has nevertheless been pulling in tourists from far and wide.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly07EnhancedTitle">Antonov Rings (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly07EnhancedDescription">Believed to have been formed from a shattered moon, this asteroid band is so rich in dust that it helps fund all the system's new developments.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly08EnhancedTitle">Huygens Rings (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly08EnhancedDescription">A rich, multi-colored band of asteroids surrounds this planet. Reflecting the star's light in green, gray, purple, white, and blue, they are a highly prized tourist destination as well as a ready source of minerals and alloys.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly09EnhancedTitle">Hollow Planet (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly09EnhancedDescription">Although new, deeper caves are still being discovered to this day, the majority of the planet's vast caverns have been explored, reinforced, studied, and repurposed for industry, research, housing, or as ready-built deep bunkers for your military.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly10EnhancedTitle">Ice-10 (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly10EnhancedDescription">A rare form of ice that is caused by water crystallizing under high pressures, Ice-10 is interesting for its thermodynamic properties - which have now been thoroughly studied, such that the fascinating substance is now a focal point of local industry.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly11EnhancedTitle">Permanent Monsoon (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly11EnhancedDescription">Once a very wet and very difficult environment, a concerted effort to partially terraform the planet has lessened the intensity of the winds and storms - except where they provide bountiful power from wind generators.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly12EnhancedTitle">Metallic Waters (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly12EnhancedDescription">Almost dirt-free, the hard, gleaming surface of this planet used to make agriculture difficult and potentially poisonous. Recent improvements in soil development, however, have eased the problem.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly13EnhancedTitle">Aurora Waves (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly13EnhancedDescription">The gleaming, multi-colored auroras that once caused such headaches have been not only tamed by magnetic shielding, but are now valued by the scientific community as a source of new discoveries in atmospheric sciences. Their beauty, thankfully, remains.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly14EnhancedTitle">Dense Atmosphere (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly14EnhancedDescription">Lava planets in particular, due to the continual combustion and high temperature of their crust, have atmospheres that are dense in organic compounds. Though it renders them a challenge to colonize, this anomaly also helps to increase the agricultural output.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly15EnhancedTitle">Psychoactive Air (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly15EnhancedDescription">With an atmosphere that was once saturated by complex chemical compounds, life on this planet was challenging. Application of terraforming technologies, however, has rendered the effects of the air less intense.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly16EnhancedTitle">Geothermic Activity (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly16EnhancedDescription">Applying enormous amounts of energy and grappling with gravitational alterations, the previously uncontrollable geothermic activity of the planet is not only manageable, but actually useful since every new factory can have its own dedicated geothermal generator.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly17EnhancedTitle">Seismic Activity (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly17EnhancedDescription">By manipulating the magnetic core, stabilizing continental drift, and improving construction techniques, the problems in daily life caused by seismic activity have been largely solved - and on top of this, the active fault-lines work to dredge up Dust from within the planet's upper mantle.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- 18 is Long Season (Negative)  -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly19EnhancedTitle">Meteor Strikes (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly19EnhancedDescription">The previously named "killer satellites" are now less like assassins and more like goalkeepers. Thanks to cheap and robust sources of energy and innovations in shield technology, incoming meteors are captured and mined for their valuable Adamantian deposits.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- 20 is Polar Tempests (Negative) -->
  <!-- 21 is Strong Magnetic Field (Negative) -->
  <!-- 22 is Kessler Syndrome (Negative) -->
  <!-- 23 is Acid Rain (Negative) -->
  <!-- 24 is Irradiated (Negative) -->
  <!-- 25-27 are moons  -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly28EnhancedTitle">Hostile Fauna (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly28EnhancedDescription">While the beasts of this planet were first described as "giant," "primal," and "impressive," these days the adjectives would tend to "companionable," "obedient," and "just the right size to ride on."</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly29EnhancedTitle">Ancient Ruins (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly29EnhancedDescription">Search teams discover ruins of one of the many ancient civilizations that have risen and fallen since the birth of the universe. Trade, tourism, and research could potentially benefit from this rare find.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly30EnhancedTitle">Dust Lode (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly30EnhancedDescription">Once a base or battleground of the Endless civilization, their nanotechnological 'Dust' is omnipresent in the ground and atmosphere.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly31EnhancedTitle">Coral Reefs (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly31EnhancedDescription">Picturesque, rich, and fascinating, these lush reefs beautify the planet, provide sources of food, and are of interest to tourists (once they have been declared either non-lethal or only partially lethal).</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly32EnhancedTitle">Cyber Flora (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly32EnhancedDescription">A hybrid species that grew from Dust-infected lichen, this nearly indestructible plant can be found thriving even in the harshest conditions. Its beautiful, glossy sheen and interesting bio-technical properties create both a stunning environment and a source of scientific knowledge.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly33EnhancedTitle">Strange Fossils (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly33EnhancedDescription">What strange beasts were these! Science Officers have discovered the remains of long-dead creatures that appear exceptional in every way -- size, variety, eating habits, and number of limbs. Anthropologists and cosmologists are eager to study these finds</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly34EnhancedTitle">Microfactories (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly34EnhancedDescription">Now that the control codes for the Endless microfactories have been deciphered, they can be programmed to help with local building work as well as food production.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly35EnhancedTitle">Mutated Flora (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly35EnhancedDescription">An example of biodiversity gone berserk, this planet shows a variety of plant mutations of every size, shape, color, scent, flavor, and psychoactive effect that one could imagine. Some of the more notable results include rich food supplies and ecstatic gourmet chefs.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly36EnhancedTitle">Low Gravity (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly36EnhancedDescription">Local architecture has evolved to take advantage of the low gravity - soaring bridges and towering needle-like spires are the order of the day, and all available with low-cost materials.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly37EnhancedTitle">Deserted Cities (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly37EnhancedDescription">An eerie reminder of yet another lost civilization, deserted cities are scattered across the surface of this planet. Even stranger, many of the buildings and machines are still in working order. If a planet had been conceived to make scientists and engineers happy, it is this one.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly38EnhancedTitle">Molten Springs (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly38EnhancedDescription">Blessed--or cursed--by volcanic activity close to the surface and a metal-rich crust, geysers of molten metal spew their very dangerous and very valuable contents from numerous points on the planet. Industry and commerce can clearly benefit from this bizarre geology.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly39EnhancedTitle">Shattered Crust (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly39EnhancedDescription">The surface of this planet is a riot of cliffs, chasms, ridges, and spikes. While the broken surface means that many mineral resources can be easily mined, it also means that transport and construction will be challenging.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly40EnhancedTitle">Komatiite Volcano (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly40EnhancedDescription">A thorough study of the local geology has revealed ways to trigger the formation of new komatiite volcanoes on demand. Industry leaders now regard the planet's upper mantle as a sort of vending machine: Insert explosives, receive magnesium.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly41EnhancedTitle">Propitious Seasons (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly41EnhancedDescription">This is not merely a planet that has the benefit of an axial tilt that produces seasonal variations in weather; the seasons and their associated climates lend themselves well to agriculture.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly42EnhancedTitle">Humeris Insidentes (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly42EnhancedDescription">This planet was inhabited by a highly advanced race that died off when a massive volcanic eruption induced a prolonged winter. The knowledge of their civilization was meticulously documented and stored in bunkers scattered across the planet. Clearly, they expected to rise up after the winter and continue their evolution. Sadly, the bunkers sit unlocked and unused, and the people have returned to the dust. Their knowledge, however, is yours to explore.</LocalizationPair>
  
    <!-- 43 is Poor Soil (Negative)  -->
	<!-- 44 is High Gravity (Negative)  -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly45EnhancedTitle">Behemoth Song (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly45EnhancedDescription">This strange planet emits natural sound and magnetic waves that imitate musical frequencies. The melodies can only be heard by ships in orbit with all electronics powered off, and their poignant beauty is said to be overwhelming.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly46EnhancedTitle">Talking World (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly46EnhancedDescription">There is a continual series of radio wave transmission from variable sites on the planet. Though they appear to be artificial and thus have some purpose, the transmitters have yet to be identified and the code or language remains an unsolved mystery.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly47EnhancedTitle">Fearful Symmetry (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly47EnhancedDescription">Archeological studies have revealed the origin and purpose of this world's symmetry: It was once used by the Endless as a setting for planet-scale games of nation development, expansion, and war. The symmetrical structure allowed for both "players" to have identical prospects. Real life, of course, is neither fair nor balanced.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly48EnhancedTitle">High-Energy Plasmasphere (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly48EnhancedDescription">A high-energy planetary ionosphere generates a particularly powerful plasma shield that naturally deflects incoming charged particles or projectiles. This field is not only a boon for scientific study, but is also a great source of natural energy as it can be harnessed as a continuous power source.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly49EnhancedTitle">Dust Halo (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly49EnhancedDescription">Though these vast fields of Dust obey the properties of fluids and appear to react to stimuli, they do not consume or replicate so they do not qualify as "living". Questions still remain as to whether they are sentient, however, for they do seem to react to most electromagnetic waves. Regardless, they are a boost to science and Dust, and their presence is always welcome.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- CRESCENT ANOMALIES -->
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly50EnhancedTitle">Artificial Life (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly50EnhancedDescription">Maybe it is the combination of billions of precise factors, or maybe it is pure luck, but every attempt to create artificial life on this Crescent seems to succeed.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly51EnhancedTitle">Dust Accretor (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly51EnhancedDescription">Large quantities of Dust can be found in the dark nooks of this Crescent, as some of the materials used in its construction seem to attract ambient Dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly52EnhancedTitle">Flickering Matter (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly52EnhancedDescription">As a material construction created by an immaterial being, sometimes this Crescent flickers and loses its materiality for a few moments. Although this is fortuitous for the understanding of matter itself, it may not be such good news when what you are trying to build disappears unpredictably.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly53EnhancedTitle">Pseudo-Atmosphere (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly53EnhancedDescription">A pseudo-atmosphere appeared during the creation of this Crescent. The way light passes through it creates unique visuals, so fascinating that even the most scientific minds tend to become aesthetes.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- WONDER ANOMALIES -->
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder1EnhancedTitle">Dust Nebula (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder1EnhancedDescription">A warning beacon into the entire nebula rich with Dust tells its story. Due to poorly-controlled research, a strain of Dust ran wild and self-replicated out of control. By the time it was reined in, entire planetary systems had been converted to Dust, and no food remained for the handful of surviving researchers that left that grim note.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder2EnhancedTitle">The Seventeen Thousand Islands Bridge (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder2EnhancedDescription">An archipelago of natural islands that span the gap between planet surface and space, hanging in the darkness like glittering stepping stones. The source of the power that maintains the islands in position is unknown, but many speculate that Endless technology is responsible.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder3EnhancedTitle">The Fallen Gardens (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder3EnhancedDescription">A space graveyard for vast structures of unknown provenance, the Fallen Gardens are a twilight world of ancient technology long forgotten and dormant. Some speculate the structures are starships of once-marvelous engineering now consigned to rust, strange mottled patches of fungus and vegetation crawling across their surfaces. Others claim they are the sloughed skins of Gods. What is certain is that the gardens are far from dead.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder4EnhancedTitle">The Platform of Ys (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder4EnhancedDescription">The world was once the greatest shipyard of the concrete Endless. The skies above the planet darkened with the enormous spacedocks that worked day and night, building and repairing fleets. While much of the technology is lost, the platforms still provide both living space and planetary defense.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder5EnhancedTitle">Tree of Worlds (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder5EnhancedDescription">Your species' finest bioengineers have, at last, worked out how to duplicate this magnificent tree - admittedly, only with this planet's unique geology, and only on a much smaller scale. However, on this world at least, buildings and even entire cities can be grown rather than constructed.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder6EnhancedTitle">Tunneled Slipgates (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder6EnhancedDescription">A natural anomaly whose probable existence is less than zero, this series of natural quantum-linked transport gates create “tunnels” from the planets’ surfaces to various points in the star system. This piece of space-time is full of bridges, shortcuts and holes, allowing rapid transport throughout the system.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- RUIN ANOMALIES - REDUCED -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeReducedTitle">Large Debris Field (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeReducedDescription">The site of a major engagement between warring empires, the space surrounding this system is filled with debris of all types and sizes.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumReducedTitle">Medium Debris Field (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumReducedDescription">The site of an engagement between enemy fleets, there are noticeable chunks of debris floating in the system's space.</LocalizationPair>
  
    <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallReducedTitle">Small Debris Field (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallReducedDescription">Twisted metal remains and scorched plastics drift here, a reminder of a previous skirmish.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionReducedTitle">Pre-galactic Architecture (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionReducedDescription">A minor civilization that resisted assimilation was conquered here, and signs of the battles remain.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeReducedTitle">Gutted Pirate Stronghold (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeReducedDescription">A thriving pirate colony was laid to waste here, resulting in massive devastation and debris.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumReducedTitle">Gutted Pirate Lair (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumReducedDescription">There was once a pirate hideout here, but only ruins and debris remain.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallReducedTitle">Gutted Pirate Hideout (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallReducedDescription">A small band of pirates once held this place, but they were driven out and only some debris remains.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeReducedTitle">Apocalyptic Landscape (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeReducedDescription">An enormous ground battle occurred here, and the planet will forever show the horrific scars.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumReducedTitle">Devastation (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumReducedDescription">A ground battle took place here, and the planet is only slowly recovering.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallReducedTitle">Trenches (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallReducedDescription">A minor engagement occurred here, but the evidence of battle is already disappearing.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- RUIN ANOMALIES - ENHANCED -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeEnhancedTitle">Large Debris Field (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeEnhancedDescription">The site of a major engagement between warring empires, the space surrounding this system is filled with debris of all types and sizes.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumEnhancedTitle">Medium Debris Field (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumEnhancedDescription">The site of an engagement between enemy fleets, there are noticeable chunks of debris floating in the system's space.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallEnhancedTitle">Small Debris Field (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallEnhancedDescription">Twisted metal remains and scorched plastics drift here, a reminder of a previous skirmish.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionEnhancedTitle">Pre-galactic Architecture (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionEnhancedDescription">A minor civilization that resisted assimilation was conquered here, and signs of the battles remain.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeEnhancedTitle">Gutted Pirate Stronghold (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeEnhancedDescription">A thriving pirate colony was laid to waste here, resulting in massive devastation and debris.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumEnhancedTitle">Gutted Pirate Lair (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumEnhancedDescription">There was once a pirate hideout here, but only ruins and debris remain.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallEnhancedTitle">Gutted Pirate Hideout (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallEnhancedDescription">A small band of pirates once held this place, but they were driven out and only some debris remains.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeEnhancedTitle">Apocalyptic Landscape (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeEnhancedDescription">An enormous ground battle occurred here, and the planet will forever show the horrific scars.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumEnhancedTitle">Devastation (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumEnhancedDescription">A ground battle took place here, and the planet is only slowly recovering.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallEnhancedTitle">Trenches (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallEnhancedDescription">A minor engagement occurred here, but the evidence of battle is already disappearing.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Empire Improvement -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementAnomalyReduction1EffectOverride">Cancels the negative effects of Mixed Anomalies
Allows Mixed and Ruinous Anomalies to be Enhanced
Anomaly Enhancement requires the [ecologistColored] #B0C65D#Ecologists#REVERT# to be the Primary Political Party</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementAnomalyReduction2EffectOverride">Nullifies the effects of Negative Anomalies
Allows Negative, Positive, and Wonder Anomalies to be Enhanced
Anomaly Enhancement requires the [ecologistColored] #B0C65D#Ecologists#REVERT# to be the Primary Political Party</LocalizationPair>
</Datatable>