<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">

  <!-- <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyEndlessWonder1EnhancedTitle">Husk of Knowledge (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair> -->
  <!-- <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyEndlessWonder1EnhancedDescription">Auriga housed the greatest site for the study of xenobiology ever created by the genius of the Endless. A towering achievement of industry and science, the surface and crust of the planet were a warren of laboratories, biospheres, and research centers. When the bombs fell during the Dust Wars, this enormous installation became the greatest expanse of ruins - and store of lost knowledge - in the known galaxy. Should the laboratories ever be repaired and the data recovered, the scientific benefit would be unimaginable.</LocalizationPair> -->
  <!-- <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyEndlessWonder2EnhancedTitle">Spotora's Sanctum (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair> -->
  <!-- <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyEndlessWonder2EnhancedDescription">Also known as the Icarael's Watch, this is the one laboratory in all of the Endless-controlled galaxy that had the best claim to the discovery of the science of virtualization. Spotora Ortamm and her team are credited with the first consistent, replicable method for the virtualization of a sentient mind; the notes and equipment have enormous value in spite of their age.</LocalizationPair> -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly01EnhancedTitle">Garden of Eden (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly01EnhancedDescription">The hardest thing about enhancing this planet was working out how a perfect world could be made even better. Ultimately, your ecologists took a different approach - the planet's mild seasons and lack of significant tectonic activity made it ideal for construction of a series of delicate climate-controlled domes, exhibiting the ecologies of countless other worlds from parched deserts to frozen tundras.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly02EnhancedTitle">Dust Ruins (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly02EnhancedDescription">Although the first instinct of the local industry leaders was to plunder the Dust ruins for their riches, long-term thinking prevailed, and they were instead carefully excavated and studied.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly03EnhancedTitle">Friendly Locals (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly03EnhancedDescription">Integrating the planet's native people and culture into their society from the start, and acting as guests rather than colonizers, this world's population have become more accepting of others. The multicultural society here is a wonderful working environment for all the myriad species of your empire.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly04EnhancedTitle">Rich Soil (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly04EnhancedDescription">The soil of this planet is so rich in bacteria and nutrients, and so good at promoting plant growth, that it's actually profitable to mine dirt and ship it to other planets in the system.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly05EnhancedTitle">Mineral Rich (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly05EnhancedDescription">The planet's bountiful crust has been a blessing for the economy, once the initial lawless free-for-all was reined in. Now, land deeds are correctly recorded, deep-mining operations appropriately regulated, and even most of the original pollution has been cleaned up.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly06EnhancedTitle">Hadopelagic Life (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly06EnhancedDescription">It took a lot of doing, given the frankly murderous pressures involved, but your empire succeeded in constructing an ultra-deep-sea laboratory to study this planet's unique life-forms. People being as they are, it was soon followed by the galaxy's deepest underwater hotel, a lunatic endeavor that has nevertheless been pulling in tourists from far and wide.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly07EnhancedTitle">Antonov Rings (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly07EnhancedDescription">Believed to have been formed from the shattered  remains of a once-colonized moon, this asteroid band is such a rich source of Dust that it helps fund all the system's new developments.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly08EnhancedTitle">Huygens Rings (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly08EnhancedDescription">The remains of the protoplanetary disc, and now laced through with gatherer satellites, this asteroid band provides enough exotic elements for all the system's new developments.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly09EnhancedTitle">Hollow Planet (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly09EnhancedDescription">Although new, deeper caves are still being discovered to this day, the majority of the planet's vast caverns have been explored, reinforced, studied, and repurposed for industry, research, housing, or as ready-built deep bunkers for your military.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly10EnhancedTitle">Ice-10 (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly10EnhancedDescription">A rare form of ice that is caused by water crystallizing under high pressures, Ice-10 is interesting for its thermodynamic properties - which have been thoroughly studied, such that the fascinating substance is now a focal point of local industry.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly11EnhancedTitle">Permanent Monsoon (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly11EnhancedDescription">Once a very wet and very difficult environment, a concerted effort to partially terraform the planet has lessened the intensity of the winds and storms - except where they provide bountiful power from wind and hydroelectric generators.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly12EnhancedTitle">Metallic Waters (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly12EnhancedDescription">Almost dirt-free, the hard, gleaming surface of this planet used to make agriculture difficult and potentially poisonous. Newly-developed artificial soil microbes not only sequester toxic metal salts from the water, but package and serve them up on a silver platter for local chemical industries.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly13EnhancedTitle">Aurora Waves (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly13EnhancedDescription">The gleaming, multi-colored auroras that once caused such headaches have been not only tamed by magnetic shielding, but are now valued by the scientific community as a source of new discoveries in atmospheric sciences. Their beauty, thankfully, remains.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly14EnhancedTitle">Dense Atmosphere (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly14EnhancedDescription">This world's flora and fauna, which grows rapidly to extreme sizes when in a sufficiently dense atmosphere, has been successfully exported to other worlds in the system for nurturing in special pressure-controlled farming complexes.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly15EnhancedTitle">Psychoactive Air (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly15EnhancedDescription">With an atmosphere that was once saturated by complex chemical compounds, life on this planet was challenging. These days, vast filtration stations ensure that the various psychoactive compounds are available only when they're desirable.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly16EnhancedTitle">Geothermic Activity (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly16EnhancedDescription">Applying enormous amounts of energy and grappling with gravitational alterations, the previously uncontrollable geothermic activity of the planet is not only manageable, but actually useful since every new factory can have its own dedicated geothermal generator.</LocalizationPair>


  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly17EnhancedTitle">Seismic Activity (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly17EnhancedDescription">By manipulating the magnetic core, stabilizing continental drift, and improving construction techniques, the problems in daily life caused by seismic activity have been largely solved - and on top of this, the active fault-lines work to dredge up Dust from within the planet's upper mantle.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- 18 is Long Season (Negative)  -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly19EnhancedTitle">Meteor Strikes (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly19EnhancedDescription">The previously named "killer satellites" are now less like assassins and more like goalkeepers. Thanks to cheap and robust sources of energy and innovations in shield technology, incoming meteors are captured and mined for their valuable Adamantian deposits.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- 20 is Polar Tempests (Negative) -->
  <!-- 21 is Strong Magnetic Field (Negative) -->
  <!-- 22 is Kessler Syndrome (Negative) -->
  <!-- 23 is Acid Rain (Negative) -->
  <!-- 24 is Irradiated (Negative) -->
  <!-- 25-27 are moons  -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly28EnhancedTitle">Hostile Fauna (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly28EnhancedDescription">While the beasts of this planet were first described as "giant," "primal," and "impressive," these days the adjectives would tend to "companionable," "obedient," and "just the right size to ride on."</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly29EnhancedTitle">Ancient Ruins (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly29EnhancedDescription">The ruins here have been painstakingly excavated, and are not merely valuable for trade and tourism - the species that once lived here had access to a few scientific discoveries that previously eluded us.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly30EnhancedTitle">Dust Lode (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly30EnhancedDescription">By following the traces of Dust embedded in the world's crust, our scientists have uncovered - and repurposed - the fortified subterranean bases of the Endless that put it there.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly31EnhancedTitle">Coral Reefs (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly31EnhancedDescription">This world's carefully-conserved coral reefs are now a symbol of natural beauty recognised galaxy-wide.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly32EnhancedTitle">Cyber Flora (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly32EnhancedDescription">The so called "cyber-lichen" turns out to form a natural neural network under certain conditions. This allows for vital components of research mainframes and espionage supercomputers to be grown on agar plates rather than built.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly33EnhancedTitle">Strange Fossils (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly33EnhancedDescription">Your scientists have discovered connections between the ecology of the ancient, now-fossilised organisms here and the mineral deposits in the system. Working from this knowledge, new resource veins can be uncovered.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly34EnhancedTitle">Microfactories (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly34EnhancedDescription">Now that the control codes for the Endless microfactories have been deciphered, they can be programmed to help with local building work as well as food production.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly35EnhancedTitle">Mutated Flora (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly35EnhancedDescription">We've finally catalogued exactly which of the absurd profusion of flora on this planet are toxic, allergenic, or violently motile. The gourmet food industry is more diverse than ever, and being an experimental chef requires less hazard pay.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly36EnhancedTitle">Low Gravity (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly36EnhancedDescription">Local architecture has adapted to take advantage of the low gravity - soaring bridges and towering needle-like spires are the order of the day, and all available with low-cost materials.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly37EnhancedTitle">Deserted Cities (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly37EnhancedDescription">With the archaeologists' work finally finished, reconstruction and resettlement of the world's deserted cities has begun. Many buildings have been preserved in their original state, as monuments to those who came before.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly38EnhancedTitle">Molten Springs (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly38EnhancedDescription">Refineries built over the planet's miraculous molten springs extract and refine valuable materials from the gouts of white-hot metal - although a few have been left pristine as spectacular (if dangerous) tourist destinations.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- I can't think how to fit Hyperium into this one, since it's a compound generally found in the oceans or atmosphere, not the crust. -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly39EnhancedTitle">Shattered Crust (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly39EnhancedDescription">The surface of this planet is a riot of cliffs, chasms, ridges, and spikes, now traversed by soaring bridges, pierced with spectacular tunnels - and offering wonderful views to airships full of tourists.</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly40EnhancedTitle">Komatiite Volcano (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly40EnhancedDescription">A thorough study of the local geology has revealed ways to trigger the formation of new komatiite volcanoes on demand. Industry leaders now regard the planet's upper mantle as a sort of vending machine: Insert explosives, receive magnesium.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly41EnhancedTitle">Propitious Seasons (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly41EnhancedDescription">The cities on this planet have been designed with the seasonal weather in mind, so no-one is too hot or too parched in the summer or too cold, wet, or depressed from lack of sunlight in the winter. </LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly42EnhancedTitle">Humeris Insidentes (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly42EnhancedDescription">Now that all of the knowledge banks and valuable archaeological finds from this planet's bunkers have been extracted, catalogued, stored and studied, the bunkers themselves - miles upon miles of subterranean tunnels - can be repurposed as historically interesting, if unusual, housing.</LocalizationPair>
  
    <!-- 43 is Poor Soil (Negative)  -->
	<!-- 44 is High Gravity (Negative)  -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly45EnhancedTitle">Behemoth Song (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly45EnhancedDescription">Orbital habitats have been constructed after the model of opera houses and amphitheatres, to allow everyone to experience the planet's haunting, ethereal song.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly46EnhancedTitle">Talking World (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly46EnhancedDescription">Dedicated signal backtracing and code-cracking efforts have revealed the origin of the radio transmissions, although not their purpose - they appear to be nothing but a continual sequence of numbers, spoken in a recorded voice in a language of the Concrete Endless. Speculation abounds as to why.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly47EnhancedTitle">Fearful Symmetry (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly47EnhancedDescription">Archeological studies have revealed the origin and purpose of this world's symmetry: It was once used by the Endless as a setting for planet-scale games of nation development, expansion, and war. The symmetrical structure allowed for both "players" to have identical prospects. Real life, of course, is neither fair nor balanced.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly48EnhancedTitle">High-Energy Plasmasphere (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly48EnhancedDescription">Massive pylons on planet's surface stabilize and direct the natural plasmasphere, giving the entire world a shield equivalent to your strongest bunkers.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly49EnhancedTitle">Dust Halo (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly49EnhancedDescription">The question of the sentience of these vast fields of fluid, reactive Dust have been answered. Although not intelligent on their own, they are able to bond with a Dust-enhanced individual, and boost that person's awareness across the entire planet's surface.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- CRESCENT ANOMALIES -->
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly50EnhancedTitle">Artificial Life (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly50EnhancedDescription">While the source of this Crescent's beneficial effects on artificial life still remain a baffling mystery, we have decided that even if we can't understand it, we can certainly exploit it.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly51EnhancedTitle">Dust Accretor (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly51EnhancedDescription">The Dust-attracting substances of this Crescent have been identified, and although we don't have enough of the raw materials to deploy them everywhere, we've made the best possible use of what we had and turned this Crescent into a veritable dust bonanza.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly52EnhancedTitle">Flickering Matter (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly52EnhancedDescription">The intermittently dematerializing matter of this Crescent has been fully stabilized - but can still be made immaterial again on command. The industrial sectors of the Crescent now make use of machines once considered impossible, with parts moving through each other in an elegant automated ballet.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly53EnhancedTitle">Pseudo-Atmosphere (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomaly53EnhancedDescription">A pseudo-atmosphere appeared during the creation of this Crescent. The way light passes through it creates unique visuals, and we've finally found some less-easily-distracted scientists to help study the phenomenon.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <!-- WONDER ANOMALIES -->
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder1EnhancedTitle">Dust Nebula (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder1EnhancedDescription">For some time, we were justifiably cautious that the remains of the self-replicating Dust experiment here might reactivate and devour the entire system again. After extensive research, we are at last satisfied that the Dust here has been permanently rendered inert, is indistinguishable from normal Dust, and no longer needs to be kept separate from it.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder2EnhancedTitle">The Seventeen Thousand Islands Bridge (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder2EnhancedDescription">An archipelago of natural islands that span the gap between planet surface and space, hanging in the darkness like glittering stepping stones, and now covered with some of the galaxy's most desirable (and most well-defended) housing.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder3EnhancedTitle">The Fallen Gardens (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder3EnhancedDescription">Though the local religious sects were strongly against any "defilement" of the ancient structures, they were variously convinced, placated, discredited, or simply ignored. The treasures dug up from within the gardens proved to be well worth the effort, as ships built here can use lightweight hull materials and exotic drive cores not available anywhere else in the galaxy. Certain people still consider these ships to be holy relics.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder4EnhancedTitle">The Platform of Ys (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder4EnhancedDescription">The enormous spacedocks above the planet, once the greatest shipyard of the concrete Endless, have been partially restored. Although no longer able to build fleets, they provide ample staging posts for troops.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder5EnhancedTitle">Tree of Worlds (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder5EnhancedDescription">Your species' finest bioengineers have, at last, worked out how to duplicate this magnificent tree - admittedly, only with this planet's unique geology, and only on a much smaller scale. However, on this world at least, buildings and even entire cities can be grown rather than constructed.</LocalizationPair>
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder6EnhancedTitle">Tunneled Slipgates (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyNaturalWonder6EnhancedDescription">A natural anomaly whose probable existence is less than zero, this series of natural quantum-linked transport gates create “tunnels” from the planets’ surfaces to various points in the star system. Now explored and mapped, the smaller and better-concealed slipgates can be used to covertly move troops.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- RUIN ANOMALIES - REDUCED -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeReducedTitle">Large Debris Field (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeReducedDescription">The site of a major engagement between warring empires, the space surrounding this system took years to sweep clear of dangerous debris.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumReducedTitle">Medium Debris Field (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumReducedDescription">The site of an engagement between enemy fleets, the space surrounding this system took months to sweep clear of dangerous debris.</LocalizationPair>
  
    <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallReducedTitle">Small Debris Field (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallReducedDescription">Little reminder of the previous skirmish remains, even the orbital debris is no longer a nuisance.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionReducedTitle">Pre-galactic Architecture (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionReducedDescription">A minor civilization that resisted assimilation was conquered here, but only memorials remain.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeReducedTitle">Gutted Pirate Stronghold (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeReducedDescription">A thriving pirate colony was laid to waste here, resulting in massive devastation and debris.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumReducedTitle">Gutted Pirate Lair (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumReducedDescription">There was once a pirate hideout here, but only ruins and debris remain.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallReducedTitle">Gutted Pirate Hideout (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallReducedDescription">A small band of pirates once held this place, but they were driven out and only some debris remains.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeReducedTitle">Apocalyptic Landscape (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeReducedDescription">An enormous ground battle occurred here, and the planet will forever show the horrific scars.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumReducedTitle">Devastation (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumReducedDescription">A ground battle took place here, and the planet is only slowly recovering.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallReducedTitle">Trenches (Reduced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallReducedDescription">A minor engagement occurred here, but the evidence of battle is already disappearing.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- RUIN ANOMALIES - ENHANCED -->

  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeEnhancedTitle">Large Debris Field (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterLargeEnhancedDescription">The site of a major engagement between warring empires, now swept clear of dangerous orbital debris. It also provided a wealth of survey data that you used to enhance locally-built ships.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumEnhancedTitle">Medium Debris Field (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterMediumEnhancedDescription">The site of an engagement between enemy fleets, now swept clear of dangerous orbital debris. It also provided some helpful survey data that you used to enhance locally-built ships.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallEnhancedTitle">Small Debris Field (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsEncounterSmallEnhancedDescription">A reminder of a previous skirmish, now swept clear of dangerous orbital debris. It also provided a smidgin of data that you used to enhance locally-built ships.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionEnhancedTitle">Pre-galactic Architecture (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsMinorFactionEnhancedDescription">A minor civilization that resisted assimilation was conquered here, and while no trace of the battles remain, we have since learned better ways of dealing with foreign species.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeEnhancedTitle">Gutted Pirate Stronghold (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairLargeEnhancedDescription">A thriving pirate colony was laid to waste here. They left behind heavy surface-to-orbit particle cannons that have now been repaired for your own use.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumEnhancedTitle">Gutted Pirate Lair (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairMediumEnhancedDescription">There was once a pirate hideout here. They left behind laser installations that have now been repaired for your own use.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallEnhancedTitle">Gutted Pirate Hideout (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsPirateLairSmallEnhancedDescription">A small band of pirates once held this place. They left behind point defence guns that have now been repaired for your own use.</LocalizationPair>
  
  
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeEnhancedTitle">Apocalyptic Landscape (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleLargeEnhancedDescription">An enormous ground battle occurred here, and your own military has made good use of the miles of tunnels and bunkers.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumEnhancedTitle">Devastation (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleMediumEnhancedDescription">A ground battle took place here, and your own military has made good use of the remaining fortifications.</LocalizationPair>
    
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallEnhancedTitle">Trenches (Enhanced)</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PlanetAnomalyRemainsGroundBattleSmallEnhancedDescription">A minor engagement occurred here, and your own military has made good use of the trenches and craters.</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Empire Improvement -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementAnomalyReduction1EffectOverride">Cancels the negative effects of Mixed Anomalies
Allows Mixed Anomalies to be Enhanced
Anomaly Enhancement requires the [ecologistColored] #B0C65D#Ecologists#REVERT# to be the Primary Political Party</LocalizationPair>

  <LocalizationPair Name="%EmpireImprovementAnomalyReduction2EffectOverride">Nullifies the effects of Negative Anomalies
Allows Negative, Positive, and Wonder Anomalies to be Enhanced
Anomaly Enhancement requires the [ecologistColored] #B0C65D#Ecologists#REVERT# to be the Primary Political Party</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Political Event -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%PopulationPoliticalEventEnhancedAnomalyTitle">Anomaly Enhanced</LocalizationPair>

  <!-- Failure Message -->
  <LocalizationPair Name="%FailureEnhancementEcologistsDescription">Anomaly Enhancement requires the [ecologistColored] #B0C65D#Ecologists#REVERT# to be the Primary Political Party</LocalizationPair>
</Datatable>